Six,
five...
I feel like a monk with this music.
I feel like I'm in some sort of deep trance and I like it.
Ah, god damn.
I was dying of thirst.
I was putting off drinking until now because I wanted this first sip to be amazing.
And it is.
There we go.
This music right here is something called... I found a website called Singing Bowls.
Tibetan Meditation Sound Generator.
I didn't know what to put for music.
Usually I go on the menu and there's some music.
I let that play.
But this is so fitting.
I love it.
How's everybody doing, huh?
It's Friday!
Today is the day we start a new game.
Oh yeah, check the new emotes.
Or emote.
Crowwater made an animated emote with music symbols.
It's awesome.
With like a bouncing O.
Hello, cool.
The Friday, doing amazing.
Nice.
I mean, you must be on your birthday.
That's nice.
There you go, buddy.
If you don't want it, that's fine too.
So excited for the series?
Me too!
For some reason I get Rainworld vibes from the little I've seen.
So that makes me excited.
I'm really excited about this.
It's wizard hour.
True wizard hour.
Okay.
So here's the plan.
I'm gonna kick back, relax, and I'm gonna play Noida.
And I'm just gonna sit here and play this game.
And that's pretty much it.
Not much to it.
It's very simple.
Have you tinkered with BTTV emotes?
No, I haven't yet.
I have installed BTTV.
But I'm not sure how to tinker with it.
Whatever that means.
Thank you to everyone subscribing and following and doing all that.
That's awesome.
I really appreciate it.
I'm not gonna call it out while I play, though.
I'm not gonna read chat at all.
It's gonna be purely playing the game.
And immersing myself in this world that I'm curious about.
It's a Finnish game, apparently.
So, yeah.
Hey, Sir Rocco.
Thanks for subscribing.
Good to see you.
All the primes.
When did I become a mod just now?
It's your birthday.
That's why I said if you don't want it, you can tell me that and I'll take it away again.
It was just... Yeah.
It's yours if you want it.
You're pretty cool.
And you've been here forever, basically.
You don't have any responsibility.
Don't listen to Limonade.
You don't have to do anything mod related if you don't want to.
Only if you want to and you are here anyway.
Feel free.
Other than that, all good.
Okay.
So here we go.
Let's see.
Let's see if I can do this right.
So, a couple things.
I put the chat in the bottom right.
Because I saw screenshots of UI in the left or on the left side.
There were menus and stuff.
Hopefully, that's gonna be okay.
We'll have to see how that works.
Hopefully, the audio is also okay.
I need to turn off this Tibetan monk generator as well.
There we go.
Much better.
Okay.
Look at this menu screen.
Very minimal.
I love that.
I am a sucker for minimalism.
So, I went through the options real quick.
I saw this.
But people told me it's not a good idea for a first time.
So, I'm not gonna do this.
It's some kind of Twitch integration.
Apparently, it's not the best for a first time playthrough.
Graphics seem to be fine.
Audio input.
I don't know what much of this means yet.
Mod settings?
No.
I think everything is fine.
Okay.
Escape.
I will check in with you guys in maybe 20 minutes as always.
So, check how the chat window is doing in the bottom right if it's fine.
The size of it.
The audio.
All that stuff.
So, I'm just gonna jump in and play my game here.
I'm excited.
I'm relaxed.
It's Friday.
Does it get any better?
I don't think so.
Oh, before I start, let me just say I don't know anything about this game.
Nothing at all.
Except that every pixel is simulated.
I know that much.
So, that actually is very exciting.
And it's a roguelike.
That's all I know.
Let's see how it goes.
Oh, also, I will be using... I was questioning whether or not to use keyboard or gamepad.
And I googled real quick and people said keyboard for sure.
Let me activate this.
You may not believe me, but I actually don't use a keyboard per default when I use a computer.
I have to enable it every time I need to use one.
So, I just enabled the keyboard.
Alright, here we go.
It is time.
I'm gonna click new game.
Oh, wait, what?
Explore new world, the original Noida experience.
That seems pretty good so far.
Daily run, new day, new world.
Some starting items are randomized.
Every player is playing the same seed.
Be careful, you can only play once in 24 hours.
Okay, well, I think it's just this one.
A swallow.
A stinky egg.
The egg has become a jellyfish.
Electric.
Ha!
Noida.
WASD.
Okay.
Oh, I cannot... Oh, okay.
I love the look of it.
Okay.
I can just float.
Oh, I can't float forever though, look.
Top right.
Man, can I make this UI just a bit bigger?
Is that an option?
Hold on.
Options, UI scale, is that a thing?
Just... maybe not, actually.
General?
Er... I don't think so.
Actually, you know what?
It's actually fine.
It's fine.
It's not that small.
It's okay.
Okay.
We have a bar.
Equipped wand.
Oh, shit.
That's a fucking bomb.
Okay, and I only have three of those.
Oh, it made a huge hole!
Oh, shit, nice.
I like it.
What's this?
Your stomach is almost empty.
Minimally satiated, 8%.
Oh,
it's my third bar up here.
Water potion, 67% full.
F.
Just fucking kick that thing.
The mine... wait.
I?
Oh, that's an awkward key mine.
Are you kidding?
Wand.
Shuffle?
No.
All kinds of stats that I don't understand yet.
Water potion.
Equip and throw.
Mouse right on item drink.
Ah.
Spark bolt.
A weak but enchanting sparkling projectile.
It's a projectile type.
Cards 5 mana, I guess.
3 damage.
All kinds of stats.
Someone's a bomb that destroys ground very efficiently.
Okay.
Hold on.
I need to rebind that.
That's awkward.
A, F.
Input.
Controls.
Oh, wait.
Maybe it's already... Oh.
I want to use C for inventory.
Like World of Warcraft.
Is it taken by something?
Doesn't seem like it.
Ah!
Much better.
One, two.
Wait, the wheels are spinning!
Wait, what's that bar up there?
Wand recharge.
Ah, okay, I see.
I have zero dollars.
Oh, gold.
But it's a dollar sign.
That's interesting.
Nice.
Oh, that's cool!
Yo, it cuts it off!
That's actually really cool.
Look at that!
I wonder if I die if that hits me in the... What the hell is that up here?
There's some kind of particle effect.
Okay.
Can I catch fire?
Kick that shit down there.
So, hold on.
What an intro.
No music at all, just me spawning here.
Okay, I like my cape.
This is very nice.
Entered mines.
That's an enemy.
Oh, shit!
Oh, I can float.
Oh, he's sort of protected by that little ledge.
Can I get up here?
Okay, okay.
Dude, I love the graphics.
I got him!
A golden nocket!
Ten of them!
Oh, there's another one down there.
What is that?
Oh!
Ah, damn!
Ah, okay, I see.
There's like... Whoa!
Damn, dude!
Okay.
He ain't fucking around.
What is this?
Oil.
Oh, oh, wait a minute.
Is that an explosive barrel?
Oh, I'm slippery!
Look!
Oh, that's actually really neat.
Oh, look at this status.
Oil makes you slippery and more flammable.
Yeah, I thought so.
How do I get rid of it?
I'm just walking around.
It's almost over.
Ten percent?
No, it's gone.
And now I am solid as a rock.
Let me try and hit that.
Oh, what's happening?
Yo, that's awesome!
And this is like worms!
Anything can be destroyed.
But I guess a lot more complicated than worms.
Or more sophisticated, I should say.
What the hell is this?
Is this wood?
Huh, alright.
I guess I'm going to go left.
There's also something up here.
Whoop!
What did I just get?
Oh, there's something blowing over there, look.
Ooh, I want to get to that.
Whatever that is.
What is that?
Toxic sludge.
That doesn't sound good.
Well, we gotta try.
Whoa!
Okay, yeah, we take damage.
Oh, okay, that's bad.
Oh, we're still poisoned!
Shit!
Roll around, roll around.
Get the blanket.
Ten percent?
Oh, shit.
Alright, now we know.
It's for science.
That is really bad.
What if I shoot it?
No tutorials at all so far.
Oh, what is that?
Gunpowder!
Wait a minute, can I... can I kick that?
What's this?
Oh!
Oh, shit!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Come here.
Come to me.
I'm gonna fuck you up.
Watch this.
Yeah, sick!
Oh, he's bleeding!
Oh, shit!
Ah, I got him!
I got him!
I say this now.
I will not die a single time today.
This will be a flawless gaming experience.
Of course, the first time...
Oh, shit!
There was poison there.
Oh, I'm at 69 HP already.
That's bad.
Worm pheromone potion?
What's the thing below it?
Why does it look like a bomb?
Oh, there's some... Oh, no!
There's something down there.
Wait, what's happening?
It's leaking!
Wait, pheromone?
Isn't that something that attracts?
Press E to pick up.
Oh, that's a nice effect.
Oh, now I have it there.
Equipped worm pheromone potion.
And does that work the same way?
I can just...
Almost looks like I'm peeing.
Look at this.
That's such a cool effect.
Hey, it's up, dude!
This is fucking easy, dude.
Hold on.
Whoa!
What was that?
Whoa, what's happening?
Huh?
I'm scared.
Hello?
Things are exploding.
Whoops, nope.
Wait, what's this?
You feel like you're future worm food.
That's not good.
Immediate thought, is there a worm coming?
Why is there a skull in that box?
Whoa!
Paul, that scared me.
I actually recoiled my chair.
The first shot did nothing and I thought, ah, whatever, you know.
Come here.
Oh, there's a guy above me as well.
Yo, he's whole.
Oh.
Is he throwing dynamite?
Is that what I heard before?
Hey, dude.
There's a slight arc to my shot.
It's like very slight, but it's there.
It's not just a straight...
What is this?
Blood.
Something is shaking.
I wanna go up here and fuck this guy up.
Uh, my dude?
Excuse me.
He's up there.
Oh, he's guarding that thing, I think.
The glowy thing.
Hey!
What's up, dude?
Are you gonna throw that?
Okay, yeah, he is.
He definitely throws that.
69 HP still.
Nice.
Dude, I love the movement.
It's nice.
I can sort of just float.
Okay, so what is that up there?
Brickwork!
Oh, glowing stone.
Wait, I can just do this, right?
No?
Oh.
Wait, is it not getting destroyed?
Oh, it's just getting discolored somehow.
Okay.
Wait, what's this?
So, you can see the...
Okay, so you can actually see the status stuff on yourself above your character, too.
But it's also over here.
Bloody clothes protect you from fire.
You sense an increased chance of attaining critical hits.
Interesting.
What if I get all bloody?
Oh my god, look!
I'm, like, visually bloody, too.
That's a nice effect.
I like that a lot.
How do I get up there?
I guess I have to find a way around.
Oh, wait, what's this?
Oh, wait a minute, is that...
Okay.
Can I kick coal?
Kick that coal.
It kind of works, but not really.
What's this?
A plant?
Some sort.
Oh, dude.
It's the first moment in the new game.
It's always so exciting.
Cheers, everybody.
What the...
Oh!
Didn't mean to fall down.
Man, they are quick.
I got them.
And I got ten gold.
Fuck yeah.
I own that, dude.
What is that?
Is that a little mask?
Holy shit, it's a corpse.
You can just kick that shit.
Haha, that's fucking violent.
I love it.
I'm digging this.
Okay, let me go the other way.
It seems like it's sort of blocked.
Can I do anything to this brickwork?
See, that's not good.
I don't want to be future worm food.
That sounds bad.
There's nothing in here.
Do I have a map?
Hold on.
Let me actually see here.
Input.
Just quickly check.
Throw.
Track.
Auto-drag?
What?
Oh.
Yeah, okay.
Alright, I don't think there's a map.
Oh, that's bad because that means I'm going to get lost.
I'm already sort of lost.
In a new world.
What is this?
Coal.
Man, why is there so much gunpowder just lying around?
And what is that?
I don't like how that looks.
Fuck you.
I killed them.
Okay, so that is toxic sludge.
That's bad.
Why can't I see...
Like, I can see everything when I mouse over, but I can't see what these are.
These enemies.
Maybe it's a secret.
Okay, so I can't get up here, unfortunately.
Wait, I do have a bomb, actually.
Hmm, I only have two bombs.
I need to think about this wisely.
I could use it here.
It makes kind of a big explosion.
No, you know what?
I'm going to go over here.
Because I want the shiny thing.
Whoops.
I think the shiny thing is good.
Uh, no.
I think it was here.
That's where I killed the dude.
With the dynamite.
Get up here.
Oh, but how do I do this?
The bomber just bounds off, right?
Terraria style, I guess.
Ooh, hmm.
How do I do that?
That does not seem possible.
Can I really not...
What did it say?
Rusted steel.
Wait a minute.
Is that a trap?
Look at that!
Look how it's connected to something.
Is that an F?
Looks like a function character.
That makes sense.
That looks like a trap to me.
Something is connected there for sure.
Oh, you know what?
I have an idea.
I'm going to go from above.
Let's see if that's possible.
I'm just out here walking in bloody clothes.
Can I even get... Oh, wait a minute.
I can't even get through here.
Fuck me.
Okay, you know what?
Let's just try going somewhere else.
Maybe we'll find some kind of item that will allow us to go through there.
Or a different path.
I wish I could sort of look down.
I sort of can by mousing down.
Oh!
What's happening?
What the fuck is my character doing?
I'm pressing down.
He's headbanging.
He's doing something.
Okay.
Rusted metal.
Oh!
Shit!
I'm burning, I'm burning, I'm burning!
Find water, find water, find water.
Water, water, water, water!
Oh shit, I'm losing HP!
Water!
All good again, all good again.
How do I heal?
Drinking the water?
Wait.
Stomach is almost minimally satiated?
Six...
Why is there music?
Uh-oh.
Here we go, here we go.
Come here.
Come here!
Ah, you ain't shit!
I gotcha.
Okay, let's see if I can snipe these guys.
So this guy is wet right now.
Gotcha.
Next!
Gotcha!
Bye!
Aw, look at this sniper.
What's this?
Okay, new rule for myself.
Don't kick anything I see.
Just out of instinct.
Rusted metal and coal.
Is that a mushroom?
Huh.
What is this?
Okay, you know what?
New rule, don't stand on something when you shoot it and you're not sure what it is first.
Am I burning?
What's happening?
No, my screen is just flashing.
Oh god.
Oh no.
Why am I not disciplined?
That is oil and that's fire.
Me thinks that's not a good combination.
In fact, I'm not gonna go that way.
That seems dangerous.
I need to find healing.
There's a spider thingy here.
Hops.
Get cheesed.
What is that?
Is that a telescope?
Someone throwing dynamites again?
Okay, hold on.
Don't stand next to it.
We're gonna shoot it.
It's a wheelbarrow, I think.
Right?
Okay.
Cool.
Whoa, wait a minute.
Oil?
And a lamp.
Ooh, I have an idea.
Let's try something here.
Let's get to safe distance.
Oh, that did not do what I thought it would do.
For some reason I thought it would explode and blow everything up.
That would be fun.
I love when things blow up.
Oh, there is another dynamite dude.
Let me take care of this guy down here first.
Dude, these enemies are super easy.
They don't even do anything.
Yo, look at the blobs at me.
Oh my god, this is so violent.
Give me that gold.
Uh-oh.
That doesn't look good.
Come here.
It's a flaming skull.
I'm scared of what it'll do.
Whoa!
Let's not stand next to this gunpowder, maybe.
Oh my god.
That was awesome.
All the gunpowder immediately blew up.
Give me gold.
Thank you.
Okay, so it looks like the burning stops after a while.
Wait, is that the skull?
Look.
Um, there's a bunch of acid above me.
That makes me uncomfortable.
Very uncomfortable.
What do we have up here?
I hear nasty sounds.
Whoop!
What is this stuff going up?
Dude, I need to heal.
Oh, what's this?
Want?
Picked up a new magic wand.
No way.
Huh?
Burst of air.
A brittle burst of air capable of greatly pushing objects.
Huh.
Why is there three of them?
So I have three times the burst of air?
Spells per cast one?
Shuffle?
Wait a minute.
Okay, so it's like...
That's why there's three?
Oh, that thing explodes.
Watch this.
I have a plan.
Oh, there's another one.
Hey, dude.
Come here.
Hey.
Look at this.
That's odd.
Why is there a four on this?
Uh-oh, things are burning.
Oh, you're not...
Dude.
Can I...
Is it working?
Oh, Jesus.
Put out the fire!
Oh, no, I have no more water.
Can I refill it?
Whoa, almost fell down.
I want to refill my water bottle.
Whoa!
Okay.
Wait, where's that gold?
Didn't it drop any gold for me?
Do I need to activate these somehow in a sequence?
This is number four.
Wait, am I eating grass?
Wait, I'm...
What is that symbol?
I don't have time to read it.
I can do this everywhere.
Whoops.
Oh!
I'm drinking it.
Look!
Oh, that's what he's doing.
Huh.
Okay, so that's like an easier way of doing it.
Oh, can I...
Whoops.
Nope.
I want to...
Can I refill it?
Wait a minute.
Whoops.
Given that.
Let me find some water.
There's...
Can I...
Wait a minute.
Wait, what?
Minimally satiate.
It's not healing me.
Interesting.
But I definitely filled this with blood.
I don't know how I did it.
Wait a minute.
How did I just fill that?
Weird.
Let me try this.
This is...
Oh, this is worm fer...
Hahaha.
Yo, I can totally just...
How am I?
Oh, it's automatic.
Okay.
As long as it's submerged.
Look at that.
Worm ferromone everywhere.
Kind of looks like I'm peeing.
Yo, there's mushrooms here.
Can I eat those?
What?
Oh, I lost HP.
I had 21.
Uh oh, stomach's almost empty.
Can I drink this blood?
31% now?
I drink the blood of my enemies.
Hahaha, that's literally what I'm doing.
Maybe when that reaches 100% I start to heal again.
That's my theory.
Can I...
Nice.
Can I pick this up?
I don't think so.
Okay.
Gotcha.
What do we have here?
Ah, another one of those?
I kind of want to try and kick it again, but that's dangerous, isn't it?
Explode that shit.
Fire makes me afraid.
Oh, look at this guy.
Man, okay, they're actually pretty fast.
You can sort of see them in the dark.
Oh, I don't know what just happened, but I love it.
He blew up.
Oh, what's that?
There's a little bit of a ledge there.
Fuck, I want to get to that glowing thing I saw.
Also, I gotta try this.
Oh, wait a minute, can I put out fire with this?
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh!
Hello?
The air catches fire, look!
Yo, that's fucking awesome!
Okay, interesting.
Very nice.
Eat the grass.
That's also giving me food.
Eat it all.
Mmm, delicious grass.
Consume.
What if I use this on an enemy?
Oh, shit.
I should not be experimenting too much when I'm so low HP.
Especially when I promised you guys that I wouldn't die today.
Oh, it's fast!
Yeah, two shots is all it takes.
What if I hold down the button?
Okay, it's sort of fast.
Not amazingly fast, but it's decent.
What do we have here?
What is this?
Oh, it's coal, right.
Ah, wait a minute.
Entered collapsed mines.
Okay.
Can I sit in this?
Can I ride this mine cart?
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, right.
That's the kick button.
Oh, I can... I can push it?
Look.
Like a little bit.
Yo, what if I hit an enemy with that?
Hey, come here.
Oh, that's an explodey boy.
Look at that.
Boom!
Goodbye, sir.
Oh, that's not a net.
Okay.
I keep thinking this coal is part of the background.
It really messes with my mind.
So the coal is burning and that makes sense.
It's gonna burn for a long time, I guess.
Which is what coal does.
Let me...
Yeah!
I love how this is simulated.
The physics of it all is actually really impressive.
This is great so far.
I have no idea where I'm... What is my mission even?
Who am I?
You know?
We've got some music now, sort of.
Collapsed mines.
Honestly, all of this looks collapsed to me.
Man, I need to find some health.
My screen is just vibrating.
That is...
Well, it says rusted metal, but that's definitely flammable.
Blow that shit up!
Dude, blowing things up is just the best!
I love blowing things up.
How about we just try to go deep?
Oh!
Enemies!
That... What is...
That's also another one of those boxes.
What does that do?
Okay, you know what?
It seems like everything explodes.
If you're not sure about it, just assume it's gonna explode.
What is this?
Oh, is it the corpse?
Ten more gold nuggets.
How much gold do I have?
Can I see that?
Oh yeah, 227.
I see now.
227.
Okay.
What is my mission here?
Who is my boss?
Hey, dude!
Easy.
Oh, hold on.
Oh, look at this!
Bunch of water.
Now I'm gonna drink it all.
Oh, hell yeah.
We gotta figure out how to heal.
Drink it all.
What if I... Oh, when... Okay, I see now!
So when I crouch like that, it's like I can get the little remaining parts of it.
There we go.
94% were almost there.
97%?
Come on, almost there.
Drink.
98%.
Come on.
Yeah.
Get it.
106%.
You're feeling really full.
Movement is difficult.
Cause over eating.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
That's just like real life.
But where's my healing?
Alright, fine.
Oh, look at that stuff.
Hey.
Oh, okay, I'm scared.
That's fine.
See ya, buddy.
What the hell is this?
Hold on.
So there's that there.
Let me try the other way.
Oh, actually, let me go up here first.
No, you know what?
I'm gonna try this.
I need to see what this is.
Enter Holy Mountain?
Huh.
Oh!
Okay.
Oh, shit.
I was not expecting to have that much strength.
What the?
Are those fireflies?
Damn, dude.
Look at that.
I think kicking is my favorite thing so far.
This is amazing.
Let's see if we can balance these.
Yeah.
Okay, that's fine.
Okay, so what's this?
Ah, nice.
Increased maximum health by 10 and something.
Spell refresher.
Picked up spell refresher.
All spells refreshed?
Okay.
Oh, and now I can buy things.
Minus 50%.
This is true roguelike.
Want?
What the hell?
Wait, they're all wants?
They're all wants.
But they look different.
This one has a bunch of things.
This one also has a bunch of things.
Press E.
Oh, look at this one.
Minus 1.0.
Oh, it's a degree.
It's like an arc.
Minus 1?
The fuck?
0 degree?
I have no idea.
Okay, so I can't buy this one.
I can only buy this one or that one.
Which one do I want?
This one has way more stuff.
Oh, I can just...
Ah, nice.
I picked up a new magic wand.
Okay, let's see.
Double scatter spell.
Simultaneously casts two spells with low accuracy.
Disc projectile.
Summons a sharp disc projectile.
But three of them, and then...
Formation bifurcated.
Cast two spells in a bifurcated pattern.
What?
Heavy spread.
Gives a projectile a much lower cast.
Delay, but no respect to your aim.
Okay.
Oh!
There's more.
Protectiles lower?
Protectiles near you slow down?
Pinpointer.
Your spells fly faster and have lower spread.
And you have a handy sight line for aiming.
Okay.
Trick greed.
4x instead of 2x gold is dropped when death is an accident.
Alright, what's this?
Oh, perk rea...
Oh, okay, so these are like talons in a way.
Or perks, I guess.
Uh...
I want...
I think I want this.
Oh, it's a laser pointer.
Yo, that's awesome!
Hold on, hold on.
Is there a friendly fire?
We got a test.
Oh!
Okay, yeah.
Fuck, that was loud.
Okay, there's friendly fire.
That is confirmed.
Uh...
Okay.
Everything collapses.
Pretty cool effect.
I like it.
Whoa.
Coal pits.
Ohoy!
Look at these!
Wait, are they seeking?
What's happening?
Oh!
Damn, dude!
This is awesome!
Okay, hold on.
Let me spam it.
Oh, wait, it's shooting random directions?
It's not actually shooting where I'm aiming, it seems.
Wait, what is this?
Uh-oh, what's happening?
Slimy clothes protect you from fire.
The mucus makes moving around difficult.
Oh!
Yo, that's fucking cool.
I like the way they have all these different status effects.
Uh-oh.
Something is moving in the dark.
Something more is moving in the dark.
Look at these minecarts in the background with stones in them.
Or not minecarts, more like, I don't even know what that is.
Some sort of storage system?
Okay.
Coal pits.
So, something tells me the people of this land love their explosions and fire.
Coal everywhere, and gunpowder, and everyone's running around with dynamite and shit.
You know?
Hold on.
Okay.
So, I have four wands now, so if I get another one, I guess I have to replace one.
Why is that shining?
Wait, what's that?
Oh, we've got a glowy thing down there.
Hold on, let me fuck that.
Oh, hello.
Yup!
Oh!
Okay!
Right in the head.
69 HP again.
What is it with that?
Bro, this weapon right here is... kind of scary.
I don't like the way it's RNG.
It makes me scared, bro.
I'm, like, almost hitting myself in the face every time I shoot it.
The fuck?
It's awesome, though.
What's up here?
What is that?
It's all rusted metal.
Wake up!
Okay.
What's that?
Oh!
Okay!
I should have known it explodes.
Everything does.
Good to know.
Hold on.
Let me go over here.
Oh, hold on.
Oh, right.
The laser thing is on all my... uh, wands now.
Oh, this guy has a lot of HP.
Holy shit!
Maybe it is time for this.
I'm on fire!
Roll around, roll around.
Find water.
There's no water?
Who am I kidding?
Oh, wait.
I can see it here.
It's running around, actually, helping.
I'm not sure.
At least you don't...
Oh, no, what's that?
Everything is trying to kill me here, it seems.
What is this?
Lava!
See, that ain't good.
He thinks that's bad.
Ooh.
Hello!
Wait, what?
Oh, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Check this out.
I don't know what it is, but I think it explodes.
Oh.
There's some kind of toxic shit in there.
Gotcha.
Wait.
No, that wasn't wrong.
Wait, what?
Oh, interesting.
Watch this.
So, I just used this wand with the burst of air.
But I think because I was standing in front of this fire, the whole ray catches fire and I damage them with it.
For a second, I thought, wow, that guy is weak if he just collapses from a little burst of air.
But no, watch.
Oh, yeah.
Sick.
Look, I can fan the flames almost.
I think that's what's happening.
I'm actually not putting it out.
I'm making it worse.
Oh, there's a bunch of water up there.
Come on, can I?
Yo, you know what's cool about this?
It can go around corners.
I can, like, do that, you know?
But then they also randomly shoot out.
It's really fucked up.
Man, how do I get to this?
Oh, coal.
No, it is gold.
How do I get to that gold?
I guess I could use a bomb, but I only have...
Oh, I have three now!
It's recharged.
Gotcha.
So that's what it meant by that.
See ya.
Fuck, I keep equipping the wrong one.
I wanted to equip this.
Something exploded.
Something in the...
Oh!
Hello!
Okay!
He throws some kind of shit at me.
Oh yeah, you want to play...
Oh, oh!
Holy shit!
Okay!
You want to play?
Oh!
I hit myself.
Man, that fucking spell is a death trap.
Dude, come here.
What if I shoot the thing in the air when he throws it?
Did he die from that?
Sir, are you okay?
Yo, look at the effect of the projectile slowing down in the water.
How badass is that?
Look!
Isn't that just the coolest thing ever?
Do I have breath?
I do, O2, I see now.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Hold on, let me fill this up.
What does it matter if my stomach is empty?
What does it matter?
Maybe keep this at like 65 or something.
Not 100 because...
Oh, maybe actually do 100, just not over 100.
97.
I don't know what will happen if I don't, but I think it's a good idea to do it.
Maybe I'll just move slower or something if I'm hungry.
Or parched or starving, whatever.
Okay.
What do we got up here?
Okay, so I'm starting to think there's no way to heal in this game.
It is literally just you can only heal in between levels or something.
You know?
So you have to be super careful.
Yo, there's a huge place over here.
Very dark area.
Uh-oh.
Shoot that thing.
Oh, look, it's spraying poison!
How badass is that?
Okay.
Nice.
Oh, wait a minute.
It's water with toxic sludge on top.
Wait, I can just shoot it away.
Oh, hello!
Sup, dude?
Hey!
Oh, okay, okay, okay!
My dude!
Would you like some...
What?
You like that?
Come here.
He also has a gun.
Uh-oh.
Got it!
Look at that.
Look at the skills.
Where'd this guy go?
Is he there?
I can't tell.
Hello?
Hello, sir?
Can I get you a gun?
I don't want to pick up his gun.
Whoa!
I have to remember, I can just hold down the button.
Oh, somehow I'm less accurate when I do that?
When I hold the button down, I'm less accurate, it seems.
Oh, okay, hold on, we got something here?
Wait a minute, let me...
Fuck you.
Man, it's always on the other side of some kind of...
Maybe I should try the thing now.
Here we go, here we go.
You ready?
Sir?
I will not die here today.
Come here.
Man, you can float for a long time.
That thing's on fire.
Did it just go in the water?
Like, on purpose?
To stop the fire?
That's amazing, if that's the case.
Hold on, let me try...
Is that lava?
It is.
Yeah!
Here, put out the lava.
Make obsidian.
Yo, is this...
steam?
Okay!
I was about to say smoke, but close enough, I guess.
Okay.
Oh!
Look at the Dodger Master 4000.
How do I see his HP?
Gotcha!
Oh, but wait!
Can I jump in the water?
Yeah!
Okay, that gets rid of the toxic shit.
Nice.
We are almost dead.
14 HP.
Gotcha!
Give me that money.
Dude, I need money!
For the next checkpoint?
Look how I automatically float to the surface.
That's kind of nice.
Okay, so it looks like these guys don't throw any projectiles.
They just want to hit me.
Are they constantly respawning or something?
Woo hoo!
Okay!
Don't let them get too close.
They do a charge attack.
Yeah.
Oh!
Okay, I see now!
I see!
There was a little bit of a nest there of some sort.
Let's get rid of that.
Whoops!
Fuck you!
How do I deal with that?
Efficiently.
Okay, he's down.
What if I just shoot up?
I know approximately where it is.
Oh, it's dripping lava?
It's leaking lava!
What kind of a nest is that?
Gotcha!
Oh, look at that!
They are filled with lava!
That's so cool!
What a cool enemy.
Oh!
Holy shit!
Not bad, not bad.
Come on, when are you dead?
Thirteen...
I'm so scared.
Oh!
Okay, okay.
Hold on, I have an idea.
And we are going to remove this lava down there.
Ah, look at that!
It totally works.
In fact, put water everywhere here.
This is awesome!
Look at this shit!
Call me crazy, but I somehow spawned more water than I took.
Right?
That seems a little weird.
Man, when are you dead?
Oh!
Right in the face!
I have one HP!
I think it's ogre.
It may be ogre.
Hail Mary play, coming up.
Where are you, where are you?
If I so much as touch a bit of that toxic sludge, I'm done for.
I'm so scared.
How about I don't interact with that thing up there?
I've changed my mind now.
Maybe I just go down.
What do we got, what do we got?
I heard something?
Exquisite me?
Oh!
I have an idea.
Nice!
That is a definite way to gain access.
No!
Cause of death?
Fire.
You are dead.
Click here for stats.
Oh, cool.
207 gold.
50 minutes.
Depth 280 meters or 18 meters.
Places visited four.
49 enemy slain.
Max HP 110.
Nice!
So, I guess this game is all about going deeper.
You know, what maximum depth can you achieve?
Something like that.
Wait, progress?
Oh, secrets found.
Keep talking.
Bomb.
Spark bolt.
What's this?
Pin pointer.
Oh my god, wait.
Ah, these are enemies.
Heiko horta.
That's so Finnish sounding.
Let me see if I can pronounce this.
Tapra hisläinen.
And this is a...
Surtur...
Surturli kerpenen.
Hemis.
Lepakko.
Heiko limanuljaska.
So, I actually had a friend from Finland called Heiko.
With one... no, two Ks I think actually.
Unless I'm remembering wrong here.
Maybe I'm actually wrong.
Okay.
Burst of air.
Very good.
Okay, pretty cool.
Alright, let's do a quick check here.
How has the audio been and is the chat positioned correctly?
Is everything fine with that?
I'm gonna open chat in like 10 seconds.
Hold on, I need to minimize to actually see this.
Whoops, I clicked something when I minimized.
Audio wonderful.
Is it peaking too much when I yell in the audio?
Because I think that was a bit of an issue when I played Undertale.
At least in the first VOD.
I feel like there was a lot of...
What do you call it?
It's peaking a lot.
Or something.
I mean, I am peaking, yes.
But...
Okay, it's good.
There's a no-spoiler quality of life setting I should enable.
Does everyone agree there's a no-spoiler quality of life?
If everyone says yes now, I will do it.
I'm all for that stuff.
Yes?
Yeah?
I mean, it's just a setting.
Okay, let me see.
Wait.
Oh, shit.
I guess I do quit.
Motherfucker.
It quit the game.
I wanted to quit to the menu.
Damn it!
All right, I go back in.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, which setting?
I actually looked at this.
That seems pretty cool as well.
But it did say that it can make the game crash.
That made me a little worried.
Material on mouse.
I guess here.
Show hovered material next.
Oh!
Oh, it's like I see.
So instead of having it in the top, I can have it next to the mouse.
Ah.
Allow firing of once while inventory is open.
Lock mouse inside window.
Click on.
The replay recorder is great to quickly check.
Ah, okay.
That's actually cool.
You know what?
I will do that.
Press F11 to save.
Replay.
To save a replay at any point in the game.
Okay, gotcha.
Got it.
Oh, it makes a gif or something?
That's awesome.
Okay, cool.
Is that it?
That's the setting, right?
I think we're good otherwise.
Cool.
Okay.
I am gonna jump back in.
And dude, that was fun.
That was fun.
I'm liking the style.
I like the slow progression feeling of this game, where it's just like one step at a time, you know?
Very minimal music.
Here you go.
No explanation.
No tutorial.
Here's a world.
Have fun.
Reminds me a little bit of Rain World.
And I love that.
Oh, wait.
Do I do a new game or...
Oh, I guess I do.
Oh, wait.
No, no, no.
What about the stuff?
What about the secret stuff I found?
I think it's just something that is...
Hmm.
Okay, yeah.
We're back.
Cool.
Awesome.
Oh!
Oh, that's different now.
Energy Sphere.
A fast arcing projectile.
And a bomb.
What's this?
Acid Potion.
I guess I should not drink that.
You know what?
Let me try and go left.
What?
Oh, that...
You know what?
That's actually really nice.
Having the thing next to the cursor is actually big.
Thank you for that.
Oh, look at this.
Eat the mushroom.
Mmm, delicioso.
Very good.
Wow, look at this here.
Hello.
Look at that.
It's just soil.
Oh.
Hello?
Oh, it's a tree!
Oh!
Wait a minute.
Wiggling Egg.
Something wiggles inside.
Really?
Uh...
It's a worm and it just flew off.
Diamond Brickwork.
Eternal Wealth.
Curse of Greed.
You gained three times gold, but I didn't get to...
Cursed?
I'm cursed?
Wait, oh!
Huh?
Portal back to the mountain.
Wait a minute, I want to go...
Wait, am I cursed with...
Cursed Rock?
Oh, no!
Really?
Oh, wait, is it spreading from here?
Or is it everywhere I step?
Oh, that is scary!
Is it coming for me?
Oh, it's coming!
Okay.
This is bad?
You gained more gold, but a curse will haunt you.
Oh, that's not good.
I don't like that.
I do not like that.
What do these three discs mean?
Right mouse button.
Wait, what does right mouse button do?
Shit!
We gotta go...
Oh, we gotta go quick!
Exquisite me.
Let me through.
Entered mines.
Oh, okay, here we go.
We're straight into it.
Oh, there's explosives everywhere?
Oh, my God!
Fuck you!
Oh, whoa, it explodes things!
The curse!
Who's gonna explode the thingy?
Run!
Get all the gold.
Shit, son of gold, though.
I'm getting a lot of gold.
Blow it up.
Hello.
Get all the gold.
Ah, the curse hits me!
The curse is...
Ow!
Oh, run!
Fuck!
Holy shit!
Blow it up before the thing blows me up.
What is happening?
Go through the thing!
Bomb it!
I wanted to jump into the portal.
Goddamn!
From material cursed rock.
Dude, that was crazy.
Let's see here.
That was fun, though.
Max HBO hunt.
Total deaths.
Oh, no, not the total death counter.
I don't want this here.
This is not good to be here.
That was crazy.
Wait, save death replay?
Let's try that.
Why is my head stuck in the rock?
Look!
I'm just hanging there now.
What the hell?
Return to game.
New game.
Okay, so we just go like that.
Okay, man.
Okay.
This is awesome.
Hold on, I want to go back here.
I want to see that again.
Uh, I want to get that egg.
I have a feeling that the worm that spawned is going to be on my side.
And it's going to fuck everything up.
Everything in sight.
So for that reason, I'm going to...
Oh, yeah, I have...
Oh, there's new things now.
Magic missile, ten of them.
A fiery explosive projectile.
And then we have spitter bolt.
A short-lived magical bolt.
Yeah, I can see that.
Doesn't go too far, but I hopefully do more damage with it.
I should pay attention.
Oh, I can also press tap.
I was just used to pressing tap in games.
I did it all automatically.
Okay, let's do this again.
I got it.
Oh.
Wait a minute, let's try this.
Okay.
Can I go higher up?
That looks not...
Oh, actually, dude, check this out.
Oh, it doesn't make a hole.
Okay, I was trying to rest in that hole and then keep flying.
Fuck.
All right.
Wait a minute.
Hold on here.
Oh, that takes a while to recharge.
Holy shit.
Fungus.
Look at all the grass sort of flowing downhill.
Okay.
Can I...
Wait, what's this?
Soil.
Huh?
Oh, what the fuck?
What's happening?
Huh?
I'm burning.
I'm poisoning slowly the...
Oh, no.
Shit.
I thought I had water on me.
I was trying to douse water on myself.
Okay, it goes away.
It goes away.
Quicker than I thought.
Come on.
Oh, and this is bad.
Oh, shit.
Okay, there we go.
All right, this is not a good start.
But it is what it is.
We move on.
Actually, hold on a second.
Let me try here.
Can I get up here?
Oh, yeah.
Actually, that was a little ledge.
Oh, can I stand on these?
I can't.
Hmm.
No, there's no way.
Unless... does this work here?
Oh.
Hey,
look at that shit.
What do you say to that?
Wow.
There's some strength in that kick.
Oh.
Huh.
Cool.
It's a snowy peak.
What's on the other side?
Huh.
Okay.
Can I sprint somehow?
Oh, whoa.
Excuse me.
Was that rushing water sound blood?
Very weird.
Oh, okay.
I can go down here.
But wait a minute before we do that.
What the hell is that?
There's something up there, too.
I'm too curious.
Shit.
Okay.
At least I don't take fall damage, I don't think.
Oh, barely.
Jesus.
Oh, look at this stuff.
There's all kinds of things up here.
Floating islands.
Anything more?
Huh.
Isn't that weird?
Is this one of the secrets, then?
I want to find secrets so bad.
I gotta say, I love the style of graphic in this game.
Oh, the ocean.
Are you enemies?
The sound is muted underwater, that's awesome.
Oh, wait, what is that?
Oh, wait, we don't have a lot of O2.
What if I do this?
Oh, cool.
What is that?
Metal?
Wait, I'm doing damage to it?
I'm doing damage to it.
Look how slow it is.
Okay, I have one left, I should probably save it.
Wait a minute.
Get some air?
Down.
Oh, okay, that explodes.
I have 10 HP now.
But you know what, this is fine.
This is an exploratory mission that we're on here.
Just to see, just to get a feeling for the lay of the land.
You know?
Like, where are we going?
Everything is crumbling here.
Isn't that interesting?
Is that a bridge in the background, look?
Okay, you know what, let's try and head down.
Oh, never mind.
That does not seem feasible.
I'm just gonna keep going, I have no idea where this is going, this is awesome.
Let's have a sip.
What's that?
Enter the desert.
The air feels hot, uh oh.
That's not good.
Am I gonna take damage?
Excuse me.
Hold on, can I?
Oh, oh, wants, items, spells.
Wait, what?
What?
Oh, okay, it's just music.
Granite.
Oh no, I can't go here, this is all blocked.
Okay.
But there was another entrance over here, where the air felt hot.
I feel like my outfit here is very fitting for the desert.
I look like one of the sand people.
Oh, there's nothing here either, what the hell?
Well, at least I can't get to it.
I guess we keep moving on this little expedition of ours.
Can I eat the sand?
Cactus maybe.
Okay, so it's part of the background, I can't actually affect it.
What?
Arrow up, down, down?
Down, down, down?
There's something going on here.
Down, down.
Huh, weird.
And then we keep moving.
I feel like I'm not, it's not intended for me to go here yet or something.
I feel like I'm out of place.
Obviously the game wants me to go into the mines.
But I say no.
I shall go to the bone wall.
Whatever that means.
Not much of a wall, if you can just walk over it.
Now I'm wondering, what bone did this belong to?
You know, what kind of creature was that?
Because that seems pretty crazy.
Hop, hop, hop.
Weird little spell we have there.
Uh...
Eh, excuse me?
Uh-oh.
Oh, it's some kind of temple?
Hello?
Let me in.
Oh.
Okay.
I don't think my one shot with this wand is actually gonna let me through.
So...
Yeah.
Oh, actually.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
Let's see if we can't enter up here somewhere.
What's that?
Ground, granite ground.
I guess there's some kind of different layers of softness or something, so these materials.
Like, this is not doing anything to it.
But my other wand is doing something to it.
Look how big this is!
This is crazy.
Oh.
Hello?
Are you good or bad?
Press E to pick orb.
What's...
Oh, cool.
That was a cool effect.
Emerald tablet of Thoth.
The necessity of concealing the art is one of the chief anxieties of alchemists.
We are sworn to secrecy by heaven and earth and hell.
By the four elements.
By the height and the depth.
By Hermes, by Anubis, and by the howlings of Kirkros.
An oath has been required of us to reveal nothing clearly to any uninitiated being.
Ha!
The art!
The chief anxieties of alchemists.
Okay.
So I'm very surprised by the words like Hermes and Anubis and so on.
These are actual figures from mythology.
An oath has been required of us to reveal nothing clearly to any uninitiated being.
How do I become initiated?
I wish to know of the art.
You discovered an orb of true knowledge.
Secrets of Earth's anger have been unlocked to you.
Haha!
I can kick it around!
Amoral oom!
Hello?
What did I awake in the depths?
Entered pyramid, did I really?
I don't see... the air feels hot.
Okay, am I taking damage?
It's to... we're testing!
Damage?
I'm just gonna keep walking!
I can't get in there.
This is the necessary... equipment for that.
Here we go!
Hello?
What will I find in the dark?
A dead end.
Motherfucker.
So I wonder if all of this is randomly generated.
Like, I think the mines was definitely different the second time I was there.
But this stuff up here maybe.
I don't... it must be.
That's a scorpion!
Are you evil?
Are you gonna...
Fuck you!
Okay, I can kill it.
But I know that it won't kill me, that's good to know.
That is useful knowledge.
Ooh, what do we have here now?
Hello?
Essence eater.
What?
Excuse me?
I'm afraid of it blowing up.
Yeah, it blew up.
Okay.
Interesting.
Methinks I should have done something different with that.
But...
The hell?
This is a scale!
Huh?
What?
How weird is that?
Okay.
Very weird.
I get... so all of the sand is like simulated.
Look how the sand...
is sort of moving around, it's shuffling around.
Every grain is simulated.
That's insane.
Enter the watchtower.
Oh yeah?
I shall conquer this watchtower.
I am the one who watches.
Maybe I shall not kill these, let's just leave them alone.
What's this?
It's a rock.
Oh, hold on, can I kill... wait a minute.
Yeah!
A spoolie!
Skrrrra!
Okay.
I thought maybe I could kill these scorpions with it.
Dude, this is great!
I love the exploration so far of this game, this is awesome!
Fuck you!
Good music.
Putting me at some kind of uneasy feeling, you know?
What was this place called?
Sand Temple or something?
I forgot.
Oh, that's lava?
What the hell?
I love the sound effect of the rock bouncing around the little clickety-clack.
That is so satisfying.
Wait, what am I standing on?
Notice, if I go up here, the sound changes.
Oh, never mind, it's just a soundtrack.
I thought that was a...
sound the closer I got to the top.
Okay, hold on.
Do I have enough explosives to actually get through that?
I'm gonna try this.
Okay.
Shit!
It's empty.
A fiery explosive...
Can I somehow recharge it mid-game?
Uses remaining zero.
Huh.
A wiggling egg.
Something... you know what?
Release the egg!
Pick up the egg!
Okay, good.
I'm just gonna take it with me.
I changed my mind in the last minute.
Instead of going up, we're gonna go down.
What's this?
That's probably worth a ton of money.
We're gonna go to the depths of this pyramid.
That's a dead end.
Oh, more lava.
What if I cover myself in the slime?
That set resistance to fire, right?
I wonder how resistant that is.
Are we talking immunity or are we talking reduced damage?
Can I submerge myself in that shit?
Okay, so obviously I gotta try to go on top of it like this.
That's the next step.
So I've tried from inside and up.
From inside and down.
Now I'm gonna try inside, outside and up.
Okay,
weird.
It's just sort of a lava repository.
Isn't that interesting?
Whoa.
Okay.
Our journey continues.
We have seen many sites so far on this expedition.
Why is that shaking?
So what am I looking at?
It looks like...
some kind of musical instrument, does it not?
It's on a giant stone hand!
Weird.
Huh, bling.
Load up.
Be at a safe distance.
How far away can I... Okay, so...
There we go.
I'm just out here in this land causing destruction everywhere I go.
Maybe I am angering the gods or something.
I'm curious about the alchemists.
And I wonder... Oh, here we go!
Enemies!
Oh!
Whoa!
Brother!
Whoa, it's coming!
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Yo, look at the cacti!
Wait, it's wood?
How's that?
Oh my god.
I need to get close.
I don't have a...
Oh my god!
Toymar... Toymar is his projectile.
Shit!
Okay.
Well, wait, cause of death?
Oh, right.
Nice.
Okay.
That was awesome!
Okay, here we go again.
What do I have now?
Bouncing burst.
A very bouncy projectile?
No friendly fire?
On that one, that's good to know.
Firebolt?
Ah!
Neat!
Alright, I'm gonna go in here now.
Let's actually try to follow...
Yoink!
Where the game wants me to go.
For now.
Yo, that's actually pretty cool.
Nice.
Does pretty good damage.
Okay.
Very good.
Let's try over here.
I need to be systematic.
I'm gonna start from the top and work my way down.
And there's nothing on the right, so now I'm gonna go left.
That's gotta be the way I systematically go through this.
Go as far up as we can first, and then...
Oh, but I can't go through there, unless...
Oh, wait.
Oh, neat!
Hey!
What is this?
Chaotic polymorphine potion.
Wait, polymorph?
Alright.
What if I drink it?
Oh!
I have been polymorphed.
Oh, that's interesting.
Okay.
Very cool.
Get over that.
Yoink!
Oh, dead end.
Damn it.
Okay, okay.
Very cool.
So can I put this on enemies?
We need to try this.
Excuse me?
I have snake oil for you.
Cheap, cheap, cheap.
Wait a minute, I can get through that.
Yo, I love this!
This is a good one!
I can actually get through so many places now.
Alright, maybe I shouldn't overuse it.
It's already burning, so...
Oh, look at the way the light sort of opens up here and I can see through it now.
That's a neat effect.
So this looks a little dangerous to me right now.
Hmm.
It's dripping liquid lava or whatever, fire.
But now I can get up here too.
I'm gonna do that.
Let's go here.
Okay, so now I'm on the other side here.
Nice.
I want to explore everything.
And look at this, now we're at the beginning.
This is where I spawned up here.
This is oil.
Yo, let's try something.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Fuck, I'm burning.
I was about to say go into oil, don't do that.
Oh, I'm burning a lot, I'm burning a lot.
Don't go up there, don't go up there, don't go up there.
Shit.
Put this on myself.
Hey, that worked!
But now I'm pulling...
Look at this shit!
What the fuck?
Oh, shit.
That's awesome, dude.
How cool is that?
Okay.
That's a dead end.
Nice.
And this, what do we have here?
Oh, I want that shiny thing, dude.
We're gonna get it this time.
Get rid of that thing.
Oh, that takes a lot of shots with this wand.
Weird.
I'm curious about what this means with the spells up here.
Like, so I can find spells?
In addition to all of this?
Oh, here we go.
This guy is dangerous.
Oh my god!
I have to remember, this thing bounces.
So I can technically do stuff like that.
Wow.
Oh!
Freaking cool enemy.
54 HP.
Okay, nothing here.
I like that all the places that I do explore sort of get revealed a little bit more.
And it doesn't stay dark when I get away, you know?
Huh.
That big tube of water.
See ya, buddy.
So hold on, let me see something.
There's three of these here.
So that means...
One, two, three.
Okay, I understand that.
I understand.
In fact, hold on.
Can I change...
I guess I could empty this completely and put water in here if I wanted.
That would not be a bad idea if I catch fire.
You know?
Wait a minute.
Wet clothes, but check, you're from fire.
Okay, so that's actually another thing.
Just like blood.
Oh, it's the gun guy!
Gun dude!
Gotcha.
I'm scared of him.
His projectile is super fast.
Okay.
Now we're down here.
Whoopsie daisy.
Okay.
Green slimy meat.
Hold on, can I maybe...
Oh!
Wait, what am I now?
Huh!
Yo, I can destroy things with this.
What is that?
Freezing liquid!
What the hell?
Wait a minute, what happens if I go in that, do I freeze?
What is this?
I can't read what it says, something...
I'm not sure.
I thought it said freezing smoke or something.
Replace the liquid!
Ouch.
I want to eat this thing.
Wait, am I standing in...
Oh no!
I'm an idiot.
I'm standing in the poison.
Oh, and I'm slippery as well, this is bad.
Pee on it.
Let me eat this.
I'm not sure I can do that.
So now we're actually oily, that's bad.
Oh, this is the start, nice.
Now we go here.
Oh, there's a guy up there.
Oh, I am so slippery, it's crazy.
Sir?
Come here.
Get bounced on!
Look at that.
Oh, he got hit by a stray bullet.
Very nice.
Yikes!
What do we have here?
You know what?
Empty this.
Take this.
Not bad, not bad.
I got him.
Yoink!
Give me that gold.
I need to get a lot of gold.
That's the thing.
Give me more enemies.
I want to have a million gold.
Rusted metal.
Huh.
Dude, I love that the places I haven't seen yet are not revealed.
That makes it so much easier for me not to get lost.
See, now it's revealed.
And I know I have been there.
It's awesome.
Oh, you're there!
I didn't see you!
You little bastard.
Berserkium potion.
Hello.
100% Berserkium.
What does that do?
Whoopsie!
Hold on now.
Oh, shit.
I got him, I got him.
Berserk curse affects you.
Oh, wait, that's bad.
Curse is bad.
Get rid of it.
Maybe if I put it on the enemies.
Sir?
Where'd you go?
I saw you.
What is that up there?
Something is glowing.
Dude, I love the way this liquids are simulated.
It's so cool.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Douse myself.
Dude, the dousing is legit.
That's how you get rid of those.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, what the fuck is that?
Come here.
Oh, I'm going to shoot you with the big thing.
Ah!
Oh, my God.
Shit.
Wait, I'm out?
Wait, what's happening?
There we go.
Look.
Oh, he splits.
Oh, my God.
Ah!
I think I'm dead, boys.
Shit.
Shiese.
Perkiller.
Oh.
Gia.
There's another one.
Let me bounce on you.
What?
What just happened?
Douse!
I got you.
I'm still poisoned.
Ooh!
This is tense!
Holy shit!
Fuck you!
How do I get through that, man?
That's dangerous.
I'm going to go up here.
Why is that...
Oh, berserkium.
Look at that.
It's like burning hot somehow.
Worm pheromone potion.
Yeah.
About that.
What do we got down here?
Why are there all these containers with toxic sludge and oil and water and all this stuff?
Don't even think about it, sir.
Wow, these guys are actually really quick.
Very dangerous stuff.
See, that explodes.
That explodes.
Let's be careful here.
Do not hit anything unnecessary.
Oh, look at that.
There's something over here.
What the hell is that?
Oh, oh, oh!
It's a wand.
Nice!
Just like that.
Ten shots.
Shuffle, yes.
What does that mean?
Rain cloud creates a watery weather phenomenon.
What?
Oh, how cool is that?
Yo.
Fuck yeah.
Fill my water bottle.
Fill up my canteen.
Grab it all.
Just slide through that.
Yeah, boy.
Yo, that's awesome.
What a cool spell.
Lava potion.
I mean, that's just gonna...
spray lava, isn't it?
Yep.
It is.
So, hold on.
This is cool.
Let me try something.
Did I just hit myself?
Did I just...
Motherfucker.
I think I just hit myself with...
Douse myself.
Spray me up.
Put me at maximum resistance.
Nice.
Hold on, if I do this...
No!
Wrong one!
Whoops.
Oh, oh, it's wrong one again.
Wait a minute, what did I just do?
Oh, I'm an idiot.
It's this one I wanted to try.
Not a wand.
Whoops.
Oh, wait.
Rock!
Oh, look!
It's like Minecraft, but...
it's like Obsidian, I guess.
There's a dude here.
Weird fungus pouch.
Excuse me?
Pick that weird fungus pouch.
What the hell is that?
A handy pouch for carrying powdery materials.
Okay.
Uh...
What if I drink...
Wait, what?
What if I drink it?
Oh, I can't drink it.
What if I douse myself?
Wait, is it making fungi?
It is weird fungus!
Ha!
Isn't that weird?
What's this?
Copper!
Hold on now.
I'm getting all kinds of crazy things.
This looks dangerous.
What if I lava in there?
What if I do the old pee in here?
I'm super curious, I gotta try it.
At least we have an arc we can use here.
Psst!
Wait, it didn't work!
Why did the arc lie to me?
The fuck?
Wait a minute.
Maybe it didn't work up to enough speed.
No, no, no, it totally lied to me.
The hell?
Lying arc.
Get rid of that.
Ha!
Whoa!
Fuck yeah!
Look at that!
Oh, it's burning through the thing!
It's falling down now!
Oh, whoa!
Right.
That was an explodey thing.
Is that little piece of lava gonna hurt me if I walk on it?
That one pixel, let's test.
It's not, okay.
Thank God.
Now I know that.
Don't be afraid of a single pixel.
Do not.
Oh, fuck.
That's so loud in my headphones.
Oh, my God.
Somebody's throwing dynamite.
I hear you, buddy.
I think I see him too.
Oh, man.
Why is he doing that?
Is he mining?
Oh, look.
Yeah, look.
Wait, is he killing himself?
Sir?
Oh, my God, he's right here.
He's totally gonna kill himself, isn't he?
Sir, come here.
Oh, did you see that shot?
Threading the needle.
Okay.
I have an idea here.
Sir, would you like some lava?
Where is he?
Is he right here?
I can't fucking tell.
Well, we got a...
Yoink!
Burn that coal.
Oh, here he is, here he is.
Watch this, dude.
Oh, shit.
That is for you.
Look at that.
Oh!
Dude, it's no chill.
Alright.
This is a battle, man.
This is a duel.
Come on, throw your shit.
Give me money.
Thank you.
Let me go up here.
Oh, wait.
Is that another one?
It's another wand.
What is it?
Another magic missile.
I had that earlier.
Fuck yeah, dude.
Lovely stuff.
Now I can do all kinds of things.
Wait a minute.
This is the rain cloud one.
They look the same, though, in this bar up here, so it's a little confusing.
Oh, dude.
The rain cloud is great for removing dangerous surfaces.
If I need to just cleanse an area like this, watch.
Ah, fuck.
Okay.
It always makes it right above me.
I thought I could sort of aim it.
Wait a minute.
That's why I'm going to go here.
Check this.
I'm a rain god.
Yeah, look at that.
How cool is that?
And I can fill up my water bottle.
That, dude, that is such a cool animation, huh?
So simple, but so cool.
Oh, there's stuff over there, too.
Okay, so it looks like these boxes have different...
No, I was about to say different symbols on them.
They don't.
Now that it turned a little bit, I can clearly see a skull.
So, hops, hops, hops, hops.
Explode.
Whoa.
I wonder if I can get hurt by those projectiles.
A little fiery projectile.
And now we do this.
Why is that not...
Come on.
Oh, yeah, it is working.
Get rid of the fire.
The fire is sort of burning its way through the pixels here.
So it's not getting hit by the water, it seems.
Dude, this is great.
I'm having a ton of fun with this.
This is just really fun.
I love the feeling of danger at every turn.
Okay, so I have been here because everything is explored.
Let me go down now and go this way.
Oh, look at that portal deeper.
Oh, okay.
So it actually says that, too.
I think that is a trap.
Watch.
Look how it sort of connects to whatever this is over here.
I guess I want.
Oh, it's an oil, too.
I don't know about this one.
You know what?
I'm going to try something drastic.
We're going to lava this bitch.
And then we're going to get out of here quick.
Actually, wait a minute.
I have a better idea.
Better idea.
I'm going to be ultra safe now.
Get rid of this fire.
Come on.
Why is it burning internally?
Okay, it's sort of working.
I think it needs to be covered entirely for that to work.
I'm going to use this to do the following.
Lovely.
Ah!
Okay, yeah.
That works.
I wanted to burn that shit anyway.
Is that going to trigger the trap?
Let's see.
Watch.
That thing is going to explode.
Come on!
I'm not sure, actually, now that I look at it.
I think we're fine.
Look at that!
Okay, which one do you want to drop?
Spitterbolt.
That's the one I had last time, I think.
I should be looking at these stats, I think.
Oh, nice.
When I mouse over, I see what's better and what's worse.
That's actually great.
I love that.
Okay, you know what?
This one is almost done anyway.
Let's replace that.
Very nice.
And then it just is left here.
Like a physical item.
That's pretty cool.
Oh, I didn't even see this thing over here.
Oh, wait.
Oh, look at it.
It's puffing out fire.
It's here.
Is it because I'm standing here?
Wait.
And this would have triggered the oil.
This would have triggered the oil.
I freaking knew it.
Let's get rid of it.
Can I destroy it with this?
I'm definitely triggering it every time I hit it.
Look at all the fire coming out of it.
Maybe I do need this.
Bye-bye.
Look, it creates all the steam that rises to the top.
How badass is that?
What a cool concept.
Hello.
Wait, is that...
That's another portal.
What the hell?
Do they lead different places?
Yeah.
I don't want to go through that yet.
I want to explore this entire region.
Absolutely everything needs to be...
Oh, hold on.
Tabula Smarragdina.
Oh, here we go.
We get some lore.
If all the mountains were of silver and gold, what would they profit a man who lives in constant fear of death?
Hence, there cannot be in the whole world anything better than our medicine.
Which has power to heal all the diseases of the flesh.
Of whose medicine?
Notice how medicine is written with a capital M.
Listen to that sound.
Oh, that's ominous.
What is this thing on top of it?
Is that a bone?
Yeah!
Oh, no, no, no!
Okay, we're fine, we're fine.
I can still read it?
Nice!
I can't pick it up or anything.
Man!
Okay.
What would they profit a man who lives in constant fear of death?
But why does that follow if all the mountains were of silver and gold?
Hence,
there cannot be in the whole world anything better than our medicine.
Okay, so it's like some kind of super medicine?
Whose medicine?
The alchemists?
Yo, that's a lot of lava.
Hot damn.
What if I were to...
Make a bridge!
Look at this shit!
Obsidian!
Oh,
you know what?
I should... I could use my rain cloud here.
That would have been ideal.
Oh, shit, I'm out.
Wait a minute.
I need more water.
Maybe I will need to go pick up that wand again.
Oh, my god.
How do I even get in that?
I have to sort of drain this of lava, I guess.
Oh, there's actually water here.
Get all of it.
Hell yeah.
Look at that.
Give me this.
Nice.
And then...
Put this...
Wait a minute.
Cancel?
What does this one do again?
Right.
I kind of like that.
I do kind of like that.
Ah, shit.
Oh, you know what?
The third one?
What is this?
Oh, I don't want that actually.
No, no, no.
Yeah.
Fuck it.
We're gonna take this.
I have two more shots of this.
That means rain.
Now we fill up this.
Nice.
And then we have for later if we need.
Probably should have made that little puddle a bit more to the right over here.
For efficiency's sake.
But it is what it is.
I love experimenting with all of these different things in the game so far.
It's really fun.
Oh, listen to that rumble.
That's nice.
What?
Oh, my God.
Huh?
I fell through somehow.
What the fuck?
I have no... Save that!
Death replay.
What the hell?
I need to see that.
Oh, no.
It doesn't...
I think I clicked it too late.
It only saved like the last, I don't know how many seconds.
Oh, no.
I have to be quick when I do that.
Hold on.
I can sort of cheat here and see what's at the bottom.
Let's wait a bit.
Look at our corpse.
Floating to the... And there's the end.
Okay.
But look at this.
Doesn't it look like there's a little pocket of air there?
Mmm.
Okay.
What are we... Oh, look at this!
Right below me!
That is a potion, I think.
Wait, swamp potion.
Okay, we gotta try this.
Drink it.
You're feeling sick, nothing stays inside.
Cause ingesting swamp?
So I'm puking.
Yeah, I guess that's what happens when you drink swamp water.
Who would have thunk?
Sparkbolt and bomb.
Oh, I like this one.
This is very nice.
This is simple and effective.
I like the sparkbolt.
Enter the mines.
We're back.
Okay, you know what?
I'm gonna play this so good.
I'm not gonna lose a single point of HP this time.
At least I'm gonna try much harder not to lose HP in the beginning, like I always do.
I crit!
Very nice.
I wonder if that's because I hit him in the head.
Why did that just turn by itself?
Hello!
Bye-bye.
So I think I tried kicking those boxes earlier.
And it immediately exploded, but I'm not sure.
I'm gonna try again.
Okay, it didn't.
So it was something else I kicked.
What if I keep kicking it?
Hey, do something.
I somehow kicked it into the coal.
Look at that!
It's buried in the coal now.
And now it's safe.
It has now been safeguarded.
It shall not explode.
Everything is good.
I do have three bombs if I need to make a huge explosion.
That's pretty cool.
What if I put swamp water on coal?
It bounces off.
What if I cover myself in swamp water?
Oh, it's just water, I guess, when you... That makes a lot of sense.
Goddammit.
Can I put this on the minecart?
On the minecart!
Scrap!
I think if I kick that one, it explodes.
I tried that once, I think.
But I need to be absolutely certain here.
I can't gaslight myself into thinking one thing, like I sometimes do.
I think that is not correct.
Grab the gold.
Now, so why is there this huge pile of gunpowder just sitting there?
Okay, so the way they'll get in here is to open there.
I can do it.
I have a bomb.
Watch.
Ka-bloom!
What an explosion.
Swamp water to the rescue.
Swamp it up!
Oh no!
Gunpowder!
Run!
Okay.
That was a bit less...
What do you call it?
Action-filled than I expected.
I thought that would explode for sure into a big explosion.
It just sort of went off like firecracker.
That's fine.
Oh no, it's a wand!
Okay, it totally looked like a potion.
Slimeball.
A dripping ball of poisonous slime.
Six damage.
Wait, how much damage does...
Oh, I have to click here.
Three damage.
This is a lot of damage.
How much damage is this?
125.
Holy shit.
That is bonkers.
Okay.
Oh!
Is that the same attack that some of the monsters have?
And look, its rate of fire is constant.
One at a time.
Because there's only one here.
If there was two, it would be pop-pop.
Pop-pop.
Scrap!
You know?
Poop-poop-poop-poop.
I don't know why.
I have that song on my mind lately.
This looks like a death trap, and I love it.
We're going to explode the shit out of this.
You know how it is.
How do we do it best?
Can this explode things?
It can.
Most certainly.
Whoa, I'm on fire.
Swamp water, swamp water.
Nice!
Look at that!
Quick reactions there.
Almost didn't lose any HP.
Now we gotta wait for this fire to burn out.
And now we have a new access path.
Yellow!
Is that cool?
It is.
Ups, ups, ups.
Hello!
Oh, I should be trying the new one.
That is a potion.
Flummoxium potion.
What the fuck is that?
Whoops.
What just happened?
Oh my god!
Nice!
Got him.
Got him!
So the way I understand the word flummox is to be confused.
Like, oh my god, I was so flummoxed by that thing I saw earlier, you know?
I am completely flummoxed.
Oh, yeah, yeah, okay, I understand.
It's totally, yeah, it's confusion.
Oh, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Yeah.
Everything is different.
Look, when I press left, I go right.
When I click right, I go, oh, that's so weird.
Reminds me of a certain thing in Terraria action.
Oh my god, it's still affecting me.
Okay, okay, not, not bad.
I like it.
What's this?
Chaotic polymorphine.
I like this one.
Let's try it again.
Yeah.
I am now a man with a mask.
Oh, is that dynamite?
Oh shit!
Blow everything up!
Quick!
Oh wait, it's not...
Oh, okay.
Yo, that's actually pretty cool.
Look at that here now.
Oh, that one has a bunch of stuff!
Triple scatter spell.
Simultaneously casts three spells with low accuracy.
I don't know if I like that.
Fire trail gives a projectile a trail of fiery particles.
Oh, there's also different types.
Projectile modifier?
Multicast?
And this is just a projectile.
Summon rock spirit.
Summons an autonomous rock ally.
What?
Hello?
Oh, ten slots?
How long do you... last?
Oh!
Okay, okay, it explodes.
I thought it was going to follow me around and protect me.
Shit.
Why am I even surprised?
Everything fucking explodes in this game.
Of course that thing would explode.
Who am I kidding?
It only makes sense.
Oh my god.
That scares me.
Let's do a swamp water.
The swamp water situation.
This shall now become a swamp.
I have deemed it so.
Yep.
Explosions going off, I don't care.
Can I walk through this while it's mixed?
Wait, is this all...
Pete?
What is that?
What does that mean?
I don't know what Pete means.
Hold on, I'm actually going to Google that.
I feel like it's a word I should know.
Pete is the surface organic layer of a soil that consists of partially decomposed organic matter.
Ha!
So, liquid bodies, in other words.
Sort of.
Stop exploding and scaring me.
Where are you?
We need to have a talk.
So that path down here is a little...
I was about to say rambunctious, but that word doesn't make any sense in this context.
I made it.
Hello!
He's dead.
He is taken care of.
Look at me, 93 HP.
I am killing it right now.
Oh my god!
I almost jinxed.
Are you down there?
Sir?
Exquisite me?
Come here.
There we go.
I love this one.
This one right here is the shit.
Straightforward, no bullshit, I understand it!
Okay, these are scary when they get close.
I have no idea how that just exploded.
Or what I just hit, but it was awesome.
Let's go up here.
Dude, I want to find more of those lore tablets.
The tabulas.
I want to learn more about this weird world.
Who are the alchemists?
And what is...
Whoops.
Excuse me.
What is the art?
My god, this is dangerous.
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
Grab that.
I love the movement.
Oh, exquisite me!
That is a fireball throwing person with a mask on.
Hello.
Oh, he's totally bugged, look at this.
You like that?
You like that, sir?
Oh shit, I'm out of...
Oh, whoa!
Okay.
Remind me what I have here.
Bombs and slime balls.
Right, I have to try the slime ball again.
He is still not dead, I don't think.
My god!
Whoa!
Okay!
My dude ain't fucking around.
What is this last one?
Oh yeah, right, this thing.
Let's try this.
Help me!
Kill the enemy!
Come on, you stupid rock!
Did it do it?
Hey!
It's exploding on something!
Go kill that guy on the right.
Some kind of eyeball man.
Hey yo, eyeball man!
I want some of this!
Oh, it doesn't actually track to the...
That's interesting.
That is very...
I gotta say.
Am I taking damage from this floating acid thing?
Oh my god, I am.
Oh, he's on the other side of a beam.
Oh, okay.
Question.
You know what I'm gonna do here?
This is gonna be crazy.
I am gonna...
Not flamoxium.
Hey, it worked!
I was hoping for some kind of explosion, but this will do.
I'm some kind of man...
I keep taking damage from something, I'm not sure what is.
What's happening?
Why am I taking damage?
Fucking put swamp water.
Oh wait, this is...
Oh, okay, it is swamp.
I thought it was toxic sludge I had in that.
That would explain everything, but...
okay.
Nice.
I wanna go up there first.
Start at the top and work my way down.
Hello!
I need to equip this one and try that.
Oh, get one shot, bro!
This one is a sick one.
I guess that's the trade-off.
It's a slow protectile.
But it does a hell of a lot of damage.
What is that?
Eat the flour.
I'm drinking the blood.
Right.
Okay, watch this.
We're gonna do it again.
Oh shit!
Wow, hello!
Oh, there's something in here.
I can steer it, look!
Yo, I'm digging through!
That's fucking awesome!
What the fuck?
This is a trap.
Watch.
Oh?
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.
Explode.
Do your thing.
Oh wait, it's electricity!
Look!
In fact, there is a little electricity symbol on it, not a look at it.
Come on!
Explode in a big arc of electricity.
Really?
It's taking damage?
It's gotta work.
Huh.
Maybe not.
I'm scared of it though.
Uh oh.
Look at all these guys.
Wait, is the gold nogget actually blocking my projectile?
I can't tell if they're dead or alive.
Okay, he's alive.
Give me that gold!
Oh, don't fall down there.
That is the portal.
Holy shit!
This guy is shooting bombs!
You like that?
Sir?
Come here.
Whoopsie daisy.
I'm scared of going in the water when it's electrified.
I think that's a valid concern to have.
Shit.
I just hit myself in the face.
Kill yourself!
Oh my god.
Gotcha!
Man, what a duel!
Thank you!
That was cool.
I like that a lot.
Oh, here we go.
Oh,
I don't have any room.
Maybe I don't like this wand.
I will replay...
Uh, this wand is bugging out now?
Look at that.
That's weird.
It's just sort of rotating.
There's something up there.
I think that's a wand.
I want more wands.
Oh, I gotta work my way in.
Okay, hold on.
I can do this.
Because I have bo- Wait!
It's empty!
The hell is this kind of a scam?
Boo!
Oh, wait a minute.
Am I dumb?
That's for you.
Oh my- I didn't mean to explode that.
But okay, okay.
Lots of acid is everywhere now.
That's great.
Swamp water!
I have no more swamp water.
Uh, I need to kill that guy.
Haps!
Swappity!
Yikes, that is mine.
And now, it's time.
Can I blow through- Don't follow me.
I'm scared of it.
Will this actually destroy- Oh!
I don't trust my own follower!
Okay.
I- Oh my god!
I still have two bombs in that one, so that's- Jesus!
Holy crap!
Brrr!
Did I just hit the bomb in the air?
That was insane.
This guy's just walking through- Don't blow the water!
Sir, come here.
There we go.
Gotcha.
What's the- Oh wait, I'm dying.
I'm dying!
Whee!
I got something.
What did I get?
Purifying powder plus soil pouch.
A handy pouch for carrying powdery materials.
Wait!
Can I pick up gunpowder with this?
Huh?
That's a powder.
Wait, what was it again?
Purifying.
First thought?
What if I'm cursed?
Can I purify myself?
A wand with...
a torch.
Lights your wand right up.
It's a passive type.
Zero management.
Excuse me?
Huh.
Okay.
Not bad.
Oh, oh shit!
Okay, it's setting things on fire.
Okay, I see now.
That makes a lot of sense again.
You know what?
In hindsight, that makes a lot of damn sense.
I need to start thinking logically here because the game is behaving very logically.
I think that's a very big boon if I start doing that.
Look at this brickwork here!
Isn't that amazing?
I love that.
There's more over here.
And the dude...
Excuse me, dude.
I have this for you.
Collapsed mines.
Gotcha.
Fuck yeah.
This is like almost a shotgun, you know?
High damage.
Not that shotguns have slow projectiles, but it's like...
It's better in close quarters, you know, because of the slow speed of it.
What's happening up here?
I hear shenanigans.
Let me double check.
I can definitely do that.
Watch.
Wait, is that leaking now?
Shit.
I thought that would reach it.
Come here.
Oh!
Swap water.
I don't have any swap water.
This...
Just cover me with this.
Cover me with that.
Okay, that works.
Okay.
Oh, I'm too fat.
Ah!
Gotcha.
Okay, so...
Yes.
Go!
Oh, this is a bad idea!
Fill it, fill it, fill it!
Oh my god, there's poison everywhere!
I'm 1 HP.
Douse!
Oh, no, look at all this!
Flammable, oh, flammable gas.
Ah, wait a minute.
What if I...
just happened to touch that?
Yike!
Burn him!
That was awesome!
I was fully expecting to die.
And I was ready for it.
Well, this works.
Bam!
He dropped a lot of gold, it seems.
Burn it, burn it.
Set it aflame.
Come on.
Okay.
Very nice, I need to collect that gold.
Oh, my dude.
Oh, whoa!
Okay, I was not expecting that to explode.
I don't even know what I just hit.
I hit the potion, I guess.
Oh, shit, don't go in there, don't go in there.
Water time.
There we go, there we go.
Water!
Why is it still exploding?
What's happening over there?
What is happening?
Oh, I'm out of water.
Rip!
What's up, guys?
Oh, he's throwing some kind of bullshit.
Oh, Molotov, I guess?
Come here.
Oh, shit!
Damn.
These guys are crazy.
Hit him.
Hopefully that hits something.
This is crazy.
I can't even go left, there's too much fire.
Oh, he's throwing things.
I think I got one of them.
One of them is down.
Oh!
I have an idea.
That's for you, sir.
Did he die from that?
I think he died from that.
Holy mountain.
I think I gotta go in here, guys.
I'm at one HP.
Whoo!
Oh, maximum heal.
And restored to 110.
Okay, gotcha.
Spell refresher, nice.
Man, these are expensive, what the hell?
Whoa!
Why are there so many of the same...
I don't understand that.
What the fuck is all that?
Look at that stuff.
Ooh!
Spells per cast, five.
Capacity, seven.
Capacity, eight.
Wait, capacity, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Ah, okay, I see.
I thought that was how many shots I have of it.
Wait a minute, where can I see that?
This one...
No, this one has...
Where do I see how many ammo it has?
Mana...
No?
Ah, use is remaining.
Okay, so wait a minute.
Oh, I can't see that then.
I can't see it.
Mana max.
Mana?
Want mana, 83.
Oh!
I think I'm gonna...
This one looks very interesting.
But this one looks like it'll do some nice stuff, too.
I'm gonna try this.
It's cheap.
Replace...
The torch.
Let's see here.
Oh no, it has 25 shots only.
Oh!
Oak.
Ah, I see, cast...
Oh, okay.
Light, mix of projectile, illuminated...
Can I...
Oh!
Wait, can I...
Hello!
Hold on a second.
Wait a minute.
Wait a goddamn minute here.
One tooth...
No, wait, huh?
Haha!
Okay!
Interesting.
Fire bolts.
So if I go like this...
Oh, look at the...
Oh wait, no.
Ah, the last one is like a light.
Look.
You see that?
There's a light following it.
That's cool.
What the heck?
So if I do this, it should fire a slime ball followed by a fire bolt.
Right?
Huh!
Okay.
Oh.
Oh, wait a minute!
Spells per ca...
Oh, holy shit.
Wait a minute here.
If I do that...
Oh, can I...
Ah, I see, I see, I see.
Okay.
Wait a minute now.
If I do that...
Are they all shooting at the same time?
Wait.
No, it's the fourth one.
Oh my fucking God!
It's... Oh, wow.
Heck yeah.
Are you kidding me?
That's insanely good.
That's awesome.
Let's do that.
And I don't even know what I want to do with that wand.
Oh, wait a minute.
Shuffle?
Oh, wait.
Oh, that's empty.
Look.
Okay, so...
Spark, spark, slime.
Wait a minute.
What if I do that?
Is that gonna do anything?
It doesn't matter.
I guess the order does matter because...
So, spells per cast, six.
That means one, two, three, four, five...
These are all being cast when I click my mouse.
And then on the next cycle...
The next one starts over here.
That's how that works.
So this is actually kind of a crazy wand now.
Right?
If I do this...
One, two, three, four, five, six.
This is like...
Insanity.
Ho!
Damn!
Although that's dangerous because this is Firebolt.
And that's presumably gonna explode shit.
Let's not do it.
Let's keep it like this for now.
This just got very interesting.
Oh, and we also got this stuff.
Hearts bestow more maximum health.
Gases near you ignite automatically.
Yeah, how about no?
That sounds like a bad idea.
Upon death, you respawn with a hundred health?
I think... I think that's important.
But...
This one is if I'm more...
If I trusted myself more.
This is more long-term.
Hmm...
Oh, man.
I trust myself?
Wait.
Wait,
I misunderstood.
Oh, I thought my maximum health would get increased now.
But wait, does that mean I can find hearts?
That will actually increase my health.
Oh, wait, is that the...
Oh, is that the health I got before?
Just before?
I see.
I understand.
Shit.
Okay.
The coal pits.
Okay, but here we go.
We have a crazy wand now.
In fact, I'm gonna put that...
Can I shuffle?
Can I...
Oh, yeah, I can do this.
There we go.
Put this at number one.
Oh, recharging.
Let's not get hit by that.
Let's play this ultra safe.
He's bleeding.
Oh, shit.
Gotcha.
Look at that.
Double damage practically.
Damn, that's brutal.
Let's not go that way.
That looks a little too toxic for me.
We're gonna go right.
What's that sound?
I hear something.
That makes me uneasy.
I don't want to explode those.
But the thing is, if I don't do it, maybe they will fuck me later.
Right?
That is the chance that I take.
We're gonna try something here now.
Oh, yeah, look at that.
Oh, it's a...
purifying powder plus gunpowder now.
That is awesome.
I don't know what purifying is.
Oh, wait, purifying?
As in...
Oh, ah, okay.
Hey.
Hello.
That's fucking awesome.
How much do I have now?
Oh, that... I used a lot on that.
Also, I need to really rebind this.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute here.
Input.
One, two, three, four, five...
Six is already awkward.
Is...
Q used?
It's not used for anything.
E is used.
R...
does not seem to be used.
I'm taking it.
F is used.
How about T?
Nice.
Let's do that instead.
QRT.
Good.
So...
QRT.
Nice.
Very good.
Look at how this powder is sort of rolling downhill.
So the purifying powder just...
turns everything into water.
Or it just removes hazards, in a way.
But then again, when I do this, I also sort of create a hazard because I have gunpowder in here.
Dude, this is awesome.
Oh, this guy is throwing dynamite.
But I have a crazy wand.
Watch.
Hello.
Yellow.
Oh.
But there is a longer recharge time between shots, so this is...
It's not actually as good as I thought it would be.
You know?
I thought it would just go pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop.
But every time with three projectiles instead of one.
Yeah.
Throw that down there.
Oh.
Explode this.
Awesome.
Oh, he's not even dead.
Wow.
Now he's dead.
Give me that money.
I need a lot of money.
We're doing well so far.
110 HP.
No problem at all.
And we are in the coal mines.
What is that?
That's awesome.
I love the physics.
Okay.
Oh, we got a dude.
Damn.
Can I...
Ah, that's too risky.
Ho ho.
He's shooting pellets.
It's a shotgun.
Ten gold nuggets.
Did he die?
He did.
Gimme.
Thank you.
So there was something up here.
A want for me.
An arrow?
Summons an arrow.
Why does it say summon?
I guess I'll find out.
Replace it with this one.
Heh.
Okay, it's...
Summons an arrow.
Oh, I can't switch around when I'm in here.
Okay, so I can only do that in between.
Okay.
I was about to say that would be crazy if I could just do that.
Wow, I actually broke it.
Wait a minute.
Am I able to...
Okay.
What's up here?
I do wonder if there's fall damage.
Ugh, barely.
Checker!
That's for you.
Oh, dodge!
I don't have water.
But I have this.
I am now a...
Oh, this is actually a bad time to be a mushroom!
Wake up, wake up!
Wait, I can float.
Shit!
Got it.
I need that gold.
Yoink!
Wow, he just died from that.
This is doing a shit ton of damage.
I can never tell whether it's poison or grass.
Is it just...
No, it is toxic sludge.
Motherfucker.
Maybe I can tell.
The difference.
So I've been up here.
Because everything is...
What do I got here?
A dude with dynamite.
Come on!
Come here.
I'm gonna try my arrow that I can summon.
Wait, did he just die?
From going in here?
That's amazing.
Can I sort of get to that gold somehow?
Oh, shit!
Yeah, I guess I can.
Using that.
Let's say I want to excavate this.
We're gonna chest something here.
How much gold will this give me?
Is it just for the picking now?
Can I...
Wait, 192?
203.
Oh, hell yeah!
Yo, that's a lot!
Hello?
That's amazing.
Can I...
What is this one again?
Firebolt.
Can I dig with this?
Oh!
We need to find...
We need to find gold veins.
Look!
Yoink!
It's mine.
Play over.
In you go.
This is too much fun.
I am loving this game.
It's getting better and better.
Okay, let's find some exposed gold.
Oh, that's a big chunk right there.
Look at it.
Oh, I'm getting to that.
Fuck yeah.
More.
Again.
Get the rest.
400 gold is what we have now.
Damn!
What's that stuff?
Oh, it's slime.
Right.
Let's keep going down.
That is something trappy.
Oh shit.
Look at this thing!
The projectile.
There we go.
Taken care of.
Now we can pass.
That's a boulder.
The hell is that?
Vibrating wood.
Okay, fine.
Damn.
Got him.
What is this?
I have no idea what I just shot.
I can go further down, but that's more up here, the two, though.
It's just acid, it seems.
Let's go down.
Whoa!
Hello!
I somehow hit that guy.
I think that was the green projectile, too.
Just rub it.
I love kicking things.
What a saddest...
What the fuck are you?
Oh, it has a kind of aura!
I think that aura is bad.
That's bad.
Get out of here!
Oh shit!
Run!
Polymorphism!
For everybody!
Get polymorph!
No?
Okay.
Got him!
I thought he would maybe be immune to damage because he was like a ghost.
Phew!
Okay, they don't fuck around.
That was tough.
Let's keep going over here.
Man, you can stay afloat a long time if you just tap the button.
What do we have down here?
Swoooop!
There's a guy down there, too!
Oh shit!
Oh my god!
It hurts!
Got him!
God damn, I'm being besieged on all sides!
Is that even the right word?
Okay, you know what?
Let's try the arrow.
Oh, you know what?
The projectile speed on that is actually insane.
What is this stuff?
Is that polymorphism he's shooting?
It's like a ninja weapon, what I got here.
Shit, I can't hit anything.
It's fireworks!
I love these enemies!
Ah, look!
There's the portal!
But I'm not going through yet.
I need to find more money.
We need maximum money before we go on.
And the good thing is, we're going to have our spells refreshed.
So I should be using everything I have.
That is... what is...
That looks like a scroll!
Wait a minute!
What's happening there?
Look at that!
Oh no, wait, that's a...
Oh,
I have become a thing.
A sniper?
Look at that!
It's like a rifle.
Very cool.
Oh, I want to go down here.
What do we got?
I love the exploration.
Got a dude?
Oh!
Oh no.
Oh, I'm getting too...
What do you call it?
Confident here.
Maybe it's time to cut my losses.
But I want to kill that guy so bad.
I got 500 gold.
Where is he?
That was insane.
That was actually a great shot.
That was fantastic.
Okay, let's find some gold I can dig.
Like this... this here seems good.
I'm going to dig it.
Yoink!
Nice!
Beautiful.
And then I'm going to do that.
Give me all the gold.
Yeah.
You can actually go through anywhere if you have the correct spells.
That's awesome.
Fuck off.
I love the little delayed damage from the green goo.
Oh, I'm scared here.
Why is everything shaking sometimes?
Hahaha.
I love this wand.
What do we got?
That explodes.
So obviously I got to explode it first before it explodes on me.
Nice.
Okay, that is a little...
Hold on, what happens if I were to do this here?
There's gunpowder in there too.
Just... purify.
Yarrrr.
That is just awesome.
Hey, and there's a lot of gold here.
Oh man, we're rich.
Holy shit.
But I don't know how much things are going to cost the next time I go through a portal.
Maybe it's a lot.
So I want to be sure that I have enough.
Okay.
Give me that.
Come on.
Up we go.
Purify.
I need to use my keybind.
Nice.
I wonder if that refills also when I go through the portal.
Probably not, but I'm going to try and note it down next time.
Okay, so we're back at the start now.
If I'm not mistaken, there's like two portals here in this region.
Also, let me destroy that.
There we go.
Love destruction.
It's the best.
Wow, nice.
Look at all the water coming through now.
Cleanse everything.
I love draining.
Oh, the draining is so satisfying.
Listen, you can hear the water rushing.
I see gold.
Hahaha.
That's so good.
Burn it.
Let me through.
Fuck yeah.
Okay, now I need to wait.
Unless... What happens if I...
Oh wait, there's gunpowder in there.
But that actually worked pretty well.
Look.
Start from the top.
Come on.
Oh, I think I'm out of gunpowder.
Ah, shit.
Don't die, don't die, don't die.
Thank God.
Oh.
I'm polymorph-ed.
I don't know what this stuff is that's coming out of me.
I think it's bad.
Oh, now...
Now I'm back.
Okay, I can go through now.
I think I should go through now.
I have 794 gold.
Let's go.
Yo!
Oh!
What the hell was that?
Increased maximum health by 10 and restored health to 120.
Wait, I thought this would restore more.
Because I picked up that one thing.
This one.
Unless that what I just picked up was not a heart.
It was something else.
Spell refresher.
Nice.
Oh, wow, there's a bunch of stuff here.
Oh, wait a sec, this is...
These are spells!
Oh, man.
Oh, dude, hold on.
Explosion on drunk enemies?
Speed up?
Yo, that sounds pretty nice.
I guess projectile speed?
Cursed sphere.
Rock.
Firebolt with trigger?
Formation bifurcated.
Yeah, I don't want that.
I know what that does.
Circle of buoyancy.
Ah, what the hell is all this?
Horizontal barrier.
I think I want this arrow.
Large firebolt.
Fuck yeah.
There's no reason not to purchase all of this, right?
Like, why wouldn't I just take everything?
Now, this one seems interesting.
Cursed sphere.
Speed.
This seems interesting as well.
I'll take it.
What is that again?
Firebolt with trigger?
Sure, let's try it.
And...
of buoyancy.
Explosion on drunk enemies.
What?
The fuck is that?
We gotta try it.
Okay, let's see.
Oh, man.
Increases the speed at which a projectile flies through the air.
Awesome.
So, if I...
Oh, wait.
No.
This one.
But wait, how does that work?
Wait a minute.
Does this change anything?
Oh, look at the...
Look at this behind me.
It's like...
Oh.
Oh, wait a minute.
I think I get it.
Watch.
Shuffle.
It shuffles the order.
Oh, shit.
Interesting.
Okay.
So, I guess it doesn't matter which order I put this here, because it's gonna be random.
All right.
Horizontal barrier?
Oh.
Oh!
I don't know why I just reacted like that.
In my mind, I was being eaten by a monster or something.
I don't understand what just happened.
Fucking hell.
I was so scared there just now.
I don't know what the fuck is wrong with me.
But okay, so it makes a barrier that hurts to go through.
And it also stops projectiles.
Watch.
Oh, no, it doesn't.
Okay.
What if I do it, like, this way?
No!
Oh, I thought it would go vertical.
I'm an idiot.
Shit.
No!
I had so many things to test.
God damn it.
That was funny, though.
Mina's projectile?
Shit.
But look at all these records that I just said.
That's awesome, isn't it?
And I got pretty far.
I like it so far.
Dude, this game is amazing.
I'm having a blast.
I need to take a quick piss, though, because I'm bursting.
Be right back.
Okay, let's go again.
I'm so excited every time I click new game to see what kind of spells I get.
Oh, look at this.
We have a new...
blood potion.
I don't think I understand the...
the eating thing in this game.
Like, satiated.
That's the thing I don't quite understand.
Bouncing burst.
That's the...
I actually like that one, too.
T and T.
Some is a small explosive.
Nice.
So it's just like those enemies.
And I guess it explodes on impact?
Is that how that works?
Hold on, let me double check.
Oh, that's great.
Love that.
Entered mines.
Okay, let's fucking go.
I'm going to murder everything now.
It's speed run time.
Well, not really.
Because I still want to explore.
I want to find more tablets.
The tablets are my jam.
They have been on my mind ever since I found one of them.
Damn, that guy was quick.
Okay, I got to take it easy.
I got to take it easy.
This is getting a little dangerous already.
The music is perfect for capturing my anxiety.
Circle of stillness.
A field of freezing magic.
Okay.
Do things move slower in here?
Circle of stillness.
How long does it last?
I can't tell.
Interesting.
Very interesting.
Circle of still...
I got to try that on the enemies.
Be still.
Come here.
Sir, I want you to...
Be still.
I'm here, come here.
Come on.
Maybe they can only jump horizontal.
Like, they can't go up.
Never mind.
Oh, they get frozen.
Fuck yeah.
Dude, that's great.
And it doesn't affect me, it seems.
Heck yeah.
Now we're talking.
I wonder if that works for enemy projectiles.
That would be incredible.
Hello.
Habra, habra.
Nice.
You there.
Good.
Oh, and now I'm back here, okay.
Can't get through there.
Okay.
Up we go.
And down.
I'm going to go to the right now.
All the way.
As much as I can.
What's up here?
Oh.
That's where I started.
I'm an idiot.
How about we go this way?
Toxic rock.
That is the stuff that was following me when I was cursed, remember?
That's bad.
That's some bad stuff.
I wonder if my purifying stuff can fix that.
Probably, right?
If anything's going to fix that, it's going to be the purification.
Oh wait, I have to go in here and then down there.
Kind of nice that I can point to things with my cursor too.
Very cool.
The hell is this?
Oh, sand.
Just a big bucket of sand.
I like it.
Treasure chest.
Oh.
That came from above.
How am I going to get to that treasure chest?
TNT, of course.
Here we go.
Whoa.
Hey, cool.
Cool.
Yo, the physics are awesome.
Did you see the way that side was cut off and then the sand?
Oh my God.
Wow.
Hell yeah.
Wait, what is the best way to do this then?
Maybe from...
Actually, maybe it's better to do this.
Oh God.
What?
Oh, did I just destroy the chest?
There's a wand inside.
Uh...
Kick the sand great.
Can I just destroy the sand?
Not really.
Goddammit.
This is a conundrum.
Let's go from below here.
I'm going to try this.
Oh, hello.
Thank you.
Nice.
I'm starting to think it's not on impact.
It is on...
After delay.
Wait, cast delay?
0.8 seconds?
I'm not sure actually.
Oh wait, I can't...
Dang it.
How the hell?
I mean, almost.
Hmm.
I need to get to that.
I need that wand.
I could wait for the sand to roll, I guess, but that's a little bit.
Oh!
Oh yeah, that totally works.
Yeah, yeah, we're doing that.
Very good.
And I... ah, not quite.
There it is!
At least the wand doesn't get destroyed.
Whoa!
What the hell?
Glitter bomb.
Summons a bomb that explodes into volatile fragments.
Ah, wait a minute, is that what the enemies have been throwing?
It actually kind of looks like that.
The thing I thought was firework.
Fire trail.
Gives the projectile a trail of fiery particles.
That is awesome.
What is this?
Always casts?
Floating arc.
Makes the projectile float above the ground.
What?
Okay.
Haha!
That looks awesome!
I have no idea what just happened.
Let's try that again.
Oh, that looks very chaotic.
That looks scary to me.
Wait, it shoots?
Oh, spells per cast too, so it actually...
Wait, why does it shoot?
Doesn't it only shoot this and...
Ah, wait, this is a modifier.
That probably doesn't count.
So it's shooting this and...
The second and the third one is what it's shooting.
This one and that one.
This is just modifying them to have this trail.
Okay.
But why does it feel randomized direction when I shoot?
That's what I don't quite understand.
Oh, look at this.
I can totally do this.
Oh, come on!
That's awesome.
Yo, dude, this is a way to get through ground.
I can pick up a bunch of oil, spray it somewhere, and set it alight.
Even though it's not actually getting through this very efficiently.
But it is doing it slowly, in a pinch, I guess.
That doesn't look good.
That's where I was before.
Let's keep going this way.
Let's just keep going.
I completely messed up this pile of sand.
I really showed that sand.
Ground toxic rock.
That explodes.
So much oil.
What's up here?
This thing... Uh-oh.
Toxic rock?
I don't like toxic rock.
But I'm going to go up there anyway, because I'm curious.
Oh.
Yeah, no.
That is not good.
Go somewhere else.
It's very quiet here, no enemies at all.
Where are all the enemies?
Gotcha.
I have a hundred gold so far.
That's not bad.
Okay.
So I wonder if there's any kind of progression between these runs.
At all.
It doesn't feel like there is.
Except, I guess, knowledge of the game.
Which is fine.
I can...
What?
Berserkium.
That is a very interesting liquid.
What if I mix it with blood?
It just sort of floats to the bottom.
I guess it's more dense.
Look at how it almost evaporates.
Is it evaporating?
Is that what's happening?
Oh, shit!
Oh!
Look at that!
I think that's the heart that was talked about before.
Gotcha.
Look at that!
What happens if I go in the Berserkium?
A Berserk curse affects you.
Am I losing?
Wait, that is totally affecting my wand.
Look!
It's like way more...
Wait, can I hit myself with it now?
No, I can't.
There's still no friendly fire, so is this good or bad?
I feel like this is maybe good for me?
Let me get through this down here.
Using TNT.
Prop!
Nice!
Ho-ho!
Whoa!
125?
That's a sick upgrade!
What the fuck?
And look, we even have stuff here.
What the hell is that?
All seeing eye.
See into the unexplored, but not everywhere.
Oh...
Oh, I don't know what...
I don't know.
Maybe I will replace...
that one for now.
Why is it rotating?
That's so weird.
Yo!
Hello!
That seems extremely useful.
Hello?
Not bad.
So, I want to experiment more with Circle of Stillness, but I...
When that's empty, I can come back here and grab that, I guess.
The dynamite, or the TNT, is actually insane as well, because it allows me to go anywhere I want, really.
Let's try it.
Oh, did I kill it?
I didn't mean to.
Fuck.
I mean, I did mean to, but I didn't mean to.
Brrr!
Ho!
Be still!
Let's see if this works.
Shoot me!
Oh, okay!
It definitely does not stop protecting tiles.
Jesus.
Okay, so they actually have to reload.
You have a little bit of an opening to do that stuff.
Okay.
Wait a minute, didn't I also have...
Let's try this one.
Hey, boys!
What?
Why does that go up?
It flows to the top!
Is that what's meant by always casts or whatever?
That's weird.
All right, well, fine, I guess.
Would you like some of...
No, this is actually kind of... This one is kind of useless.
Ow!
Yeah, ow, that hurt, that hurt, that hurt.
You can really hurt yourself with these wands, damn.
That is not a joke.
Wait, what the hell is this down here?
Teleportation?
What?
Hello?
I need me some of that.
Uh, wait a minute.
I want to change my... Be still.
I want this one instead.
You know what?
Put it here.
Fuck yeah, it's time to bomb some shit.
Can I actually bomb this?
Oh, I cannot?
What the fuck?
Maybe this down here is what's powering this.
Portal deeper, right?
I get teleported when I go into this.
Maybe this is what's powering it.
Okay.
But I'm not done here.
I only have 166 gold.
I need more.
That is not enough of my ambitions.
Oh no, not that one of these guys.
But watch this.
Blah blah blah.
See, in this case, it's kind of nice.
The fact that it always goes up.
It's got to be dead by now, right?
Let's see.
Maybe?
I'm not sure if I killed it.
It's hard to tell.
Flammoxium.
Okay.
I wonder if there's some kind of effect if I mix potions.
Like a special effect.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
That wand is chaos.
Are you dead?
You are dead.
Nice.
Look at these.
They're affected by blood.
That means they take less damage from fire.
All right.
Nothing up there.
What is that thing right there I'm standing on?
Look how this wood is burning away slowly and moving down.
That is really funny.
I see you.
I see you, sir.
So, there are two portals here.
Why are there two portals?
I wonder if it's just...
They lead to the same place.
I guess I'll find... If it's the coal mines again after, then I know it's always the same place, I guess.
Looks like there's a wand up there that I want.
Get it?
Explode!
Nice.
He's going to burn to death?
That is lovely.
And so am I soon.
Unless I pour some, uh, flamoxium on this.
Flamoxium!
Oh, no!
I hit myself with it.
I was flamoxed for a second.
Flamox!
Blood!
Oh, my God, I clicked the wrong button.
Holy shit, that was scary.
Oh my god!
Leave, leave, leave!
I kind of want to go in the toxic sludge.
Am I crazy?
I want to see what's down there.
Dude, I want to go in the toxic sludge.
It's got to be a secret.
Oh, I wonder if I'll survive long enough to fall through the toxic sludge all the way to the center.
Ooh,
probably not, right?
I feel like I should try for science.
You know what?
Let's try for science.
Fuck yeah!
Oh wait, I'm still affected!
Bloodbath!
Oh, whew!
Okay, hot damn.
Damn!
There we go.
135, baby.
And 250 gold?
That's not too shabby.
Oh, you know what?
Let's not take that yet, because if I want to test...
Wait.
Is that a chainsaw?
More bombs?
Lovely.
That is the fireball thingy?
What the hell is that?
Also, chainsaws.
So weird.
I want to try this.
No, I want to try... Okay, I have 250.
This one is half off, though.
But this is just light.
What is this?
Always casts...
Always casts electricity?
Maybe that's what that means.
I'm gonna try this one.
I want to see what the fuck the chainsaw does.
Replace that one, honestly.
Oh, that is very underwhelming.
What the hell?
Come here, let me change all you.
Dude, this is useless.
A good tool for cutting meat also has some magical properties.
So it is actually just a chainsaw?
Weird.
What if I do...
Huh.
Does this do anything?
What if I do that?
Oh, let's be careful here.
Wait.
Oh!
What just happened?
Why did that just explode?
I have no idea.
Well, this one is actually insane.
So the shuffle?
This has no shuffle.
These are both yes, this is no shuffle.
I don't actually have that many spells.
I think I want to keep it like this for now.
It also has some magical properties.
I wonder what those are.
I'm gonna rock this for now.
This is what I know.
Oh, you know what?
Wait a minute, I can do something here.
I can do this and deposit all these up here, dude.
There's no reason to leave this behind.
Can I shift click?
Oh, okay.
Lovely.
So at least this one is...
Oh, but oh, hold on.
This one is actually better because it has more slots.
So I should be using this one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hold on.
Quickly change this again, just so I can put this up here.
Yeah, nice.
Exchange that.
And now I can go crazy with things.
Bunch of... So this casts two spells per...
Oh, maybe that... Wait a minute.
Is this gonna change anything?
Magical properties.
Whoops, that's the wrong one.
Oh, okay, okay, hold on.
I thought for a second the chainsaw made the thing go up, but it's actually... Look, it's this one.
You can see this in the center.
Always casts the one that goes above a hill.
That is... Oh, that's actually amazing.
You can totally shoot around corners, Lotus.
Well, yeah, sort of.
Wait, look.
That's pretty cool, huh?
So this shoots two per.
Is this two at a time?
It is.
Fantastic.
And if I put this here, it doesn't do anything because it's only two, right?
Ah, look at that.
That is awesome.
So I wonder if this does anything other than just adding the fire.
Will it do more damage as well?
Probably set enemies a fire, right?
That would be great.
Let's do that for now.
And let's put this up here.
Let's put that there.
Oh, wait, the glitter bombs.
Now that they don't always fall up, these can be useful.
Watch.
Yeah, not bad at all.
Whoops, I didn't mean to break that up, but that's okay.
Okay, I think we're ready.
That is freaking awesome.
And what is this now?
We get to choose now something.
Revenge tentacle.
You summon a monstrous tentacle upon taking damage and gain 25% resistance against projectiles.
What a weird thing.
Okay.
Angry ghost.
An angry spirit comes to your aid, copying nearby spells and projectiles.
Uh,
fungal disease.
When near danger, you sprout fungal growth.
I don't know, man.
Maybe I want this.
I want to try the revenge tentacle.
Fuck yeah, let's see what that does in action, huh?
I love this.
Such a satisfying sound and effect.
Ah, coal pits.
That's not coal mines.
So it's always the coal pits afterward, even though I went through the toxic stuff.
Look at me walking on gunpowder.
So hold on, I need to have my specialized.
This one needs to be there.
This is my bomb thingy.
Oh, this is also bomb and this is the all seeing thing.
That's actually so freaking cool.
I guess that's really nice to know whether or not I should be digging for something.
God damn.
Did that guy just die from a nugget falling on his head or something?
That's what that looked like.
Oh wait, this always... Wait, why is it shaking?
Oh, this thing.
Oh, is that the angry ghost?
Kind of looks like the same symbol.
Oh my god.
I saw the tentacles.
Look at how it follows the terrain.
Pretty cool, but also kind of detrimental to me sometimes.
Sometimes I don't want it to do that, to do that thing, you know, because I'm aiming straight for him and it sort of bends a little bit.
That's not good.
Did that just follow the enemy?
What the hell?
Okay, yeah, this is actually annoying.
I don't like the way it bends.
I changed my mind.
I hate it.
Wait, this guy only takes damage.
Am I losing damage?
Am I taking damage right now?
What's happening?
Nothing's happening to me.
This is not doing anything.
It's weird.
I thought for sure I would be losing HP or something.
Well, I'll take it.
Not bad.
Blood me.
There we go.
Look at that blood stain on the wall.
I think one of the guys below him blew him up and died.
I'm not mistaken.
Yikes.
I'll take that.
That's for you.
Come on, blow up.
Nice.
I love dodging with the float mechanic.
It's so well done.
Explode.
Oh, that hurt.
He hit me straight in the mouth.
If you're quick enough, I don't think you get to take any damage there.
Somehow that went the other way, but that's okay.
Ah, it's already here, but I shouldn't take it, I don't think.
I need more money.
I need at least like 300, actually 400, because I saw the maximum price.
Oh, shit.
I think it was 400 that I saw in that store.
There's another one there.
Damn, they really want me to go through.
I refuse.
I still have a lot of HP.
Oh, my God.
That was scary.
I have to remember, I also have the true side thingy.
Ah, nice.
That thing just burned away so I can get to it.
I'm burning now.
This is not good.
This is what's happening.
Oh, it was my tentacles.
There's so many weird mechanics in this game.
That guy's gonna shoot me.
Are you also gonna fuck me up here?
Where's that guy?
Did he die?
I think he fell into stuff down here.
Can I grab it?
I'm poisoned.
Shh.
We're okay.
Oh, wow.
Wait, what's happening?
Why am I taking damage?
Also, the gold disappears after a while.
I did not realize that was a thing.
That's really bad.
Oh, whoa.
The good thing about the tentacles is it will show you when you take damage.
It's gonna...
Yeah.
I died from lava because the thing I killed expelled lava on death.
That's what happened.
I should have thought about that before I killed it while standing below it.
Whoops.
Let's go again.
This game is hard, man.
But it's fun.
Sparkbolt and Firebolt.
Let's fucking go.
Okay, I'm gonna try and speedrun a bit through the first area here.
It's gonna be my objective.
Find a lot of money.
Like, I don't even know, like a couple hundred.
Maybe a bit more.
And then we go through the portal and we keep doing that.
Don't be too greedy.
Oh my god.
Shit's going off.
Don't throw that at me.
Sir, come here.
You like that?
I bet you hate that.
Okay, I actually like this fireball.
Is it called fireball?
Firebolt.
Come here.
It's a one-shot, I think.
Yeah, look at that shotgun, dude.
Oh my god, it has a lot of, uh, whatchamacallit, drop off.
I got him!
Wow, that was a sick shot.
Get the money.
Oh wait, he's not dead!
What the fuck?
Oh no, that was another enemy.
Never mind.
I understand.
He was just sitting on top of him.
I thought it was his corpse being soundified or something.
That was scary.
Hello.
Oh shit.
I think he just killed his friend down there.
What's up?
Burn it all.
Oh, I wanna... you know what I wanna do.
You know what I wanna do.
Well, that was not what I wanted to do, but almost.
Oh, it doesn't blow up immediately when it hits.
That guy's gonna burn alive.
And now he's gonna die of toxic sludge.
Or not.
Oh yeah, he's gonna die.
But then the money's lost.
Got it.
Give me the... oh nice, there was more money there.
I have a dude here.
Man, I am farming these guys right now.
Can I wedge a little thing up there?
Oh, nice!
Look at that!
Oops.
Wait, what?
There's a long recharge on this.
Explode.
Oh no, I don't explode actually.
Oh yeah, do explode.
I'm on fire!
Water me.
There we go.
What is that, liquid?
Concentrated mana?
What?
You gain mana back faster.
Wait, how does the mana actually work?
I never paid attention.
Wait, what's the difference?
I'm not sure I understand.
But I can pick some of it up.
It is now... how much do I have?
96% cotton?
What if I drink it?
Whoops!
I threw it.
On accident.
Whoops.
Fuck off!
I don't need that anyway.
God dang.
I meant to drink it, damn it.
But I accidentally right clicked.
I kind of forgot that you could right click with those things and have things happen.
But now I know.
You there?
Show thyself?
Dude, I'm getting efficient money right now.
It's going quick.
This is good stuff.
Look at that.
Bunch of oil there.
What do we have here?
I'm getting way more confident now in this game.
Maybe too confident.
Ah, there's no such thing.
No such thing.
Maybe I should always have like blood on me.
That's not a bad idea actually.
Come on, bloody me up.
That way I'm resistant to fire.
But it does wear off quick, so I don't know.
That guy's on fire.
He does not have blood on him.
He made that mistake.
Got it.
I want to find more tablets.
I have a feeling there may be one tablet in every region or biome.
Whatever you want to call it.
Maybe one for each.
The hell's up there?
Oh, is that the outside up there?
It may be.
God, the movement is so smooth.
Fantastic.
It's so responsive, you know?
It just feels good.
Hello.
I need some easiest enemies in the world.
And they all drop so much money.
It's actually crazy.
Look at that guy.
He doesn't have a good day.
210 money already.
Nice.
Oh, let's be careful here.
This can turn sour quick.
That's actually something about this game, you know?
It can go from 100 to 0 real fucking quick.
Got him.
Sick.
Oh, I need to pick up the gold.
Hurry.
There we are.
What's that?
Pheromone potion.
Okay.
Nice.
Equip... Oh, 100% pheromone.
Douse thyself?
A charm affects you.
What does that mean?
I'm charming now.
I will be irresistible.
Look at the hearts on me.
Maybe I can befriend enemies?
Or doused my friend.
Unless I have to douse it on them.
Wait a minute.
Let's try this.
Sir?
That's for you.
Look at that.
Wait, he doesn't want to be doused.
Then you die.
What about this guy?
Ha!
That did mean to fall in here.
Whoops.
Doused.
There we go.
Well, well, well.
Let me not pick this up yet in case I blow myself up over here with these things.
Okay, what do we have?
Chain bolts.
That looks interesting.
Firebolt with... I don't know what that means because I never got to test it last time.
Spark bolt with... what does with trigger mean?
Chainsaw.
Bifurcate.
What's this?
Luminous drill with timer?
I like the idea of drilling.
Yes, thank you.
A pinpointed, short-ranged beam of concentrated light that casts another spell after a timer runs out.
What?
Okay.
And this?
Sea of flammable gas.
Disc... oh, disc projectile.
That sounds cool.
Sea of flammable gas.
Some is a sharp disc projectile.
Let's try it.
Um, remove these.
Let's try this first.
Oh yeah, it's definitely...
Luminous... wait, what's with the timer thing?
It's definitely drilling.
Look.
I mean, it's not exactly fast, but...
Wait a minute.
Can I combine?
Oh, but wait, it only casts one.
Shit.
So this is actually not gonna work the way I think it is.
And that's one of those.
At least this one shoots predictable projectiles now, and not like in random direction like last time.
That's not bad.
Damage 20.
And this is only three.
Yo, this is actually sick.
What if I do that?
I mean, not bad.
I think I like this.
I like this, I think.
But I kind of wish I had more wants to fill out.
That's like the issue here.
Let's get this one.
Fireball.
No wait, I have... is that the same as...
Oh, this is Firebolt.
This is Fireball.
Oh, but I have seen this before, I think.
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
I've tried that one.
Good.
This one only costs 20.
I kind of want to spend all my money.
I think that's wise.
See a flammable gas.
Chain bolt.
That sounds cool.
Whoa!
Oh, there's a long recharge on that one.
Fires a mysterious bolt that jumps from enemy to enemy.
Dude.
Wow.
Okay, so mana recharge is definitely slow right now.
Sparkbolt with trigger.
What does that mean?
Oh, fuck.
I didn't realize how much money I left.
Oh!
Oh, wait.
Wait a minute.
I think I understand.
No, it's way faster, isn't it?
Oh wait, it's not.
A weak button.
Spark, will it cast another... upon collision with an enemy?
Maybe.
Because collision with this doesn't do anything, I don't think.
Whoops.
Okay, didn't mean to do that, but okay.
There's water up there.
I can buy this or that now.
Let me buy this.
Just use all my money.
I have zero money left now.
A good tool for cutting meat.
Also has some magical problems.
I want to find out what that is.
But this is a good setup.
Wait
a minute.
What is the difference here?
Minus one.
Oh, this one costs 10 mana.
This is five.
Oh, what if we were to do this?
Oh, that's not very nice.
You know what?
Let's keep it simple like this for now and then add...
Uh, where's the crazy one I have?
That one.
25 damage.
I want to try this on my second.
Fuck it.
Let's just run with this.
What's this?
More hatred.
Creatures become more aggressive towards each other.
Oh!
Were they aggressive to begin with?
You bleed flammable gas instead of blood.
Why is this a good thing to have flammable gas?
Fungal creatures spawn from the corpses of enemies killed by you.
Cordyceps.
Oh.
Hmm.
I think I want more hatred in my life.
I would love for the enemies to fight each other.
That would be great.
Would love to see that.
Okay, let's move.
Hello.
Got a rat.
And a treasure chest.
Hot damn.
Let's see.
Triple scatter spell.
Simultaneously cast three spells with low accuracy.
A fire trail.
And summon egg.
Summon's an egg that houses a friendly creature.
Really?
Only two shots of this.
I will make it count.
I'm not sure exactly what I needed, but we will keep it on hand.
Just kill that.
Why did I just do that actually?
Maybe I should stop doing this, because now there's surfaces everywhere with this bullshit.
That was not smart.
Got him.
I got him.
Somehow.
I need to pick up his gold before it disappears.
Man, it's just rolling downhill.
Manique disappeared.
No.
Let's try this.
Sir, watch that.
Ouch.
Man, that guy is not joking.
Why is everything shaking?
He shot that himself.
That was awesome.
Oh, right.
I have that on.
Creatures become hostile toward each other.
Give me the money.
Shit.
I missed it.
Keep going.
Wait, something on the other side is trying to burn through.
What is that?
Let me try this one.
Damn, the recharge on this is kind of nuts.
Damn.
Okay.
Not bad.
I like the damage on it.
And I need that money.
Come here.
Oh, I didn't get it in time.
Shit.
Okay.
What do we have over here?
You.
Oh, shit.
I hate these things.
Get rid of it.
Oh, my god.
I don't even need to hit.
That's an amazing weapon.
Holy shit.
I think it's my favorite now.
That's incredible.
Watch that.
That's insane.
Oh, god.
Oh, wait.
It's spawning smaller ones.
That's bad.
Dang it.
Nice.
Give me that money.
There's also this big guy over here.
I want the money from.
Tell me it's not gone.
Where'd he go?
I think it's gone.
Shit.
What is this?
Oh, I'm slimy.
That's why I'm so slow.
That's a bomb.
That is a bomb.
And that scares me.
So, this one doesn't have a lot of range.
That's the only thing.
Got him.
But if you get close enough, it's like a shotgun.
It's just, they're dead.
Not bad at all.
Hello.
Ah, man.
I walked into that one.
Blood me.
Oh, wait.
That's not blood.
Shit.
I'm burning.
One HP.
This ain't good.
We need to find that portal right now.
It's a disaster.
Fuck.
Can I get through there?
Don't think so.
We just need to go down.
That's like the objective.
Down, down, down, down, down.
Oh, there it is.
Oh, that was close.
It's like more green now.
Heal me up.
110.
Wait a minute.
Did I never pick up the health from last time?
I just realized.
Shouldn't I have more than... Am I... Hmm.
What's happening here?
Am I being a dum-dum?
Magic arrow with trigger.
Electric torch.
Oh my god.
There's so many different things here.
Look how many spells cost 110 and below.
Is it adjusting to me being so terrible at the game?
It's like, you know what?
Fuck it.
Let's just make them easy and cheap.
Cluster bolt.
I do like the sound of that.
Was this magic arrow with trigger?
With trigger?
I need to understand what that means.
So if I buy this, I can't buy anything else.
So I can actually only buy one of these, it seems.
That's how much money I have.
Reduce spread.
Someone hollow ache.
I know what this one does and I don't like it.
Floating arc, not good.
Burst of air.
I want to see... What's this?
Quadruple scatter spell.
Let's try that.
Let's freaking try it.
Let's get rid of these things.
Now we have a bigger wand, I guess, but it's kind of useless because it only casts one spell.
That's bad.
But is it still gonna work?
Let's try this.
Because this is a multicast.
Wait.
Oh wait, I had the wrong one equipped.
Okay, so that does nothing.
Of course, that does nothing at all.
Notice how slow that shoots?
But if I put it here...
Wait a sec.
Oh, it has inherent stats, of course.
0.03 recharge time.
Oh my god.
Ah, okay.
I should pay a 10.
Cast delay.
Okay,
cast delay.
So I want a smaller cast delay on this for sure, right?
I think I like the second one being this.
That's like super fast shooting.
It's like a...
Well, a machine gun.
The first one I want to change.
I think.
Wait a minute.
Shuffle no.
Spread one degree.
So that's like an inherent thing as well.
So that means every time I shoot this, there's like a little offset maybe.
You know?
If I do this, it doesn't work because there's only one spell per cast, I think.
Even if I...
The order does matter to some degree.
And if I do this, it's still not good.
Ah, all right, of course.
It shoots them one after each other.
That's why that worked like that.
No, wait a minute, actually.
Hold on.
The first one is bare bones.
The second one is this disc projectile with the fire trail.
What the hell?
Okay.
So if I do this, the second one contains fire, but I don't have mana.
So wait a minute.
You see that?
That's a trail of fire.
So what does this do, actually?
Do I notice any difference?
Let's try and put this in here.
I don't understand this one at all.
Oh wait, am I digging?
No.
What the hell?
It's got to be affecting other spells somehow.
Notice how it does a little spark first.
Now it's not shooting at all, even though I have... Oh, I have no more left.
I see, I see, I see.
So what if we do this?
Ah, hold on.
Notice how if I put this in here, at the mouth of my wand, there's like a little spark now.
It's a little spark.
So what does that mean?
And now the spark comes after, look.
But this, the spark comes first.
It's like instant.
Wait a minute.
It increases the speed of it.
The recharge time is much lower now.
But why doesn't that work here?
One, two, three, four, and without.
One, two... Oh, it does work!
Holy shit, I didn't pay attention.
Well, it's very hard to notice, I guess.
It increases the rate of fire.
Okay.
So that's bad.
Oh, wait a minute.
Put this here.
What if I change these?
See, it's different.
Okay.
Dude, this is insane.
I have a digging machine, basically.
It's like the flame thingy from Worms.
But wait, yeah, so I want this... Hmm, how does this affect that one then?
Wait.
Do, do, do.
Without.
Oh, wait a recharge.
Bum, bum, bum.
And with it?
Huh, it only shoots two at a time then.
Oh, no, no, it doesn't.
Okay, that's weird.
Weird.
Fireball.
Okay, I'm definitely gonna put this one.
Here.
Like, that is crazy.
Wait, it is... Wait, is it actually digging?
I can't tell.
It doesn't... Yeah, yeah, it totally does.
It totally does.
It's just very weird.
Very weird.
I want this one here, I think.
Wait.
Yeah, that's fine.
And then we have this one.
Machine gun.
Fuck yeah, let's, let's rock and roll.
What's this?
More love.
Creatures become more friendly.
Bro.
No.
Attract gold.
Gold nuggets gravitate towards you.
No wand tingering.
Wands cannot be tingered with, but enemies may drop blood money.
Ha!
No, I, that, no.
I want this.
Let the money flow to me.
That's what I say.
Dude, experimenting with this is so much fun.
I love this stuff.
Snowy depths.
Oh my god!
I think the creatures become aggressive towards each other is having an effect here.
Also, this is slippery AF.
Oh my god.
Excuse me, sir.
That looks like a mage of some sort.
Oh my god!
Yeah, that's definitely some kind of mage.
Come on.
Arcs towards him.
Fuck yeah.
I'm scared.
Ah!
Oh!
Holy shit!
I want to get off Mr. Boneswell, right?
Holy shit.
Wow.
Those guys don't fuck around.
Holy crap.
Oh, let's see here.
These projectiles are insane.
What the hell?
Progress?
Let's see here.
Let's see the progress.
Man, there are so many spells.
Are you kidding me?
What the fuck?
Look!
It's just now daunting on me.
Like, or daunting on me.
Never.
Where's that guy I just met?
Oh, is that me?
Me, no?
Where is that motherfucker that just killed me?
I need to find you.
I've killed 37 of them.
They have not killed me once.
Oh, I can screw.
Oh my.
Oh my fucking god!
Dude!
Okay.
There's a lot of spells in this game.
Wow.
Ah.
Damn.
Okay.
I can't find the dude that killed me.
Unreal.
I think it's because I haven't killed one of them yet.
They only pop up here when I kill one of them.
That's what I think.
There are so many perks.
Dude.
This is fun, man.
Oh my.
Dude, it's been four and a half hours?
What?
I thought it was two hours.
I gotta end now.
I can't do another one.
Holy.
I'm way over time.
This is not good.
I gotta do some things.
Save and quit.
Holy shit.
People.
This game is amazing.
Let me put on the amazing singing bowls.
I'm gonna be a couple of minutes.
Singing bowls time.
How's everybody doing, huh?
I can't believe it's been four and a half hours.
That's unreal to me.
Great timing.
I've got to go as well.
You know what?
That's actually the real reason.
Reef.
I knew you had to go, so I just played it off, you know, as if I had to go.
So that's why.
I don't want you to miss a single thing.
That was so much fun to watch.
Dude, it was so much fun to play.
What the fuck?
This game is amazing.
They weren't kidding about the simulated pixels.
That is the best thing ever.
Oh, did I say singing balls?
I didn't actually mean to say that like that.
I didn't.
That was no joke there at all.
That was so fun.
It was.
This is like insane exploration.
Noida Koma.
Understandable.
It's my favorite roguelike.
Dude, I can see why maybe.
I'm curious to see how much content there is in this game, but so far this is fun.
I won 4000 potatoes gambling on your deaths.
How did you guys gamble today?
Did you just set up like he's going to do this one run?
Or I guess it's per run.
I mean, obviously I'm going to die every run.
There's no surprise there, I don't think.
So I guess you must have bet on specific things.
Ah, on what plays I would die.
That makes sense, Jen.
Yeah, that makes sense.
It's an absolute joy to watch this.
I'm so glad you guys are enjoying it.
Because I'm having a blast too.
What a cool game.
I should have known Finnish people make awesome things.
Of course, they can't make a bad thing, can they?
I'm really trying to pronounce the Finnish words as best as I can.
It was great to hear your scream when you got hurt by the vertical barrier.
You're wrong.
Rat shadow.
Don't you mean the horizontal barrier?
I was trying to do the vertical... Oh, maybe that's what you were trying to say.
Yeah, I was trying to do the vertical barrier.
I thought if I aimed up, it would make a horizontal one.
And if I aimed to the sides, it would make a vertical one.
That was what made sense in my mind.
Your Finnish pronunciation was Italian.
Fuck!
Why do I always end up sounding Italian when I pronounce things?
I have a... I have a tendency to do that.
That's for sure.
She was on point.
Was it though?
I have a feeling this game is perfect.
Dude, I have...
This is exactly something for me.
It's like Rainworld, but different.
It's like... I want to say less punishing than Rainworld.
But it's not the same either, because this is a true roguelike.
Whereas Rainworld, you make progress all the time, right?
But Rainworld feels more difficult.
So far, at least.
Like, I'm just dying to stupid things right now, because I obviously don't know the game very well.
But it's so much fun to figure it out.
Which monster scared you the most?
It's got to be the last one.
Or maybe when I turned into that worm.
That caught me off guard completely.
When I started digging the polymorph thing.
Oh my god.
Holy shit.
Heistavito.
Mamma mia.
Hey Godlieb, are you Finnish?
Or are you German?
Because I would think you were German, based on the name.
Hamis.
Hamis?
Adividachi.
The red worm was a real jump scare.
It was.
Yes.
But honestly, the biggest jump scares in the beginning were the explosions.
The random explosions happening all around me that I had no idea what was.
You know?
I'm just going boom somewhere.
I'm so excited for whatever this game has waiting for me.
You know what the funniest thing in this game so far is for me?
Just exploring.
Before I go through the portal, I love to just go through everywhere and figure things out and find all the things.
Find as much gold as I can.
Find as many wands and potions and all that.
I love this feeling of risk reward.
I love knowing that I can go through the portal now and I will sort of keep what I have or I can be a little greedy and keep going.
And I love being greedy in games like this.
That is just the funniest.
You always end up dying somewhere, right?
But it's just this feeling of gambling in a way.
It's so good.
Wow.
Thank you, Red Shadow.
Thank you for saying that.
I'm glad you're enjoying watching it.
Can we expect an Elden Ring series on YouTube?
For sure.
I'm definitely gonna play it.
And now the expansion is out too.
So I don't know when I'll play it but probably soonish, I would say.
I was actually thinking what the next game on YouTube should be.
I was leaning towards Prey.
I've been looking it up and it seems really fun.
It's like science and it's a first person so it's a little bit different.
Actually Subnautica is also first person but you know it's like a shooter I guess so it's a little bit different.
Anyway, there's multiple games I want to play.
I'm still sort of calming down from the Bloodborne.
That experience still hasn't settled with me quite yet.
I need to let it like fully absorb into me you know.
Because if I want to go into Elden Ring I want to go in completely as fresh as I can be you know.
Notebook in hand.
Fucking trying to make sense of all the lore that is happening throughout everything.
It's gonna be one crazy ride.
And I need to be prepared for that both time-wise in my life and also mentally you know with everything else going on.
If I'm playing Elden Ring I want to go hard.
Is it a better suited for stream?
Oh you're talking about Project Sunboyd.
I haven't played Project Sunboyd but I've seen a little bit of it.
Ah who was it?
Someone on Twitch was streaming it.
Ah man I forget his name.
But I saw a couple minutes of it and it looked pretty interesting.
Like a top-down zombie survival game.
It would be cool to raid a random Noida streamer.
Yes!
Should we do that?
That would be fun.
I have not played Lobotomy Corporation Hive.
Is it something that needs to go on the list?
I've started saying that so demon-casually to my friends.
You know I was joking with my friends in real life about it.
Wouldn't it be funny if that just became a thing that spread slowly everywhere?
That would be my greatest achievement in life.
If that saying would become like common.
I would also kind of hate it in a way.
Because it just sounds so demon to say that you know.
And you don't know if that's positive or not.
I think it's meant positively but who knows.
That would be pretty demon.
It's so true.
I'm trying to make that a reality.
Reminds me of...
I forget his name on YouTube but someone tried to make the... it was a joke video of course.
But the joke of... what was it?
Insano style.
That's so insane.
Something like that.
It just fucking makes me laugh.
Reminds me a bit of that.
If the president says that I'm gonna go nuts.
I love the meditative gongs.
Me too.
It's a website called...
mynoise.net and it's singing bowls.
Tibetan meditation sound generator.
It's just... it varies randomly.
It's RNG.
It just...
This is not a predetermined song.
This is all completely generated randomly on the fly.
It's weird and cool.
Joel Haver.
That's the guy.
Yeah.
Talos Principle 2 is also coming up of course.
And there's also a DLC for that now too so...
fucking awesome.
Which is kind of crazy because it's... it just came out didn't it?
Chance of Cenar is also on my list.
My list is long.
So hold on.
Did you reply about the lobotomy cooperation?
Let's see here.
I suggested.
Okay you do suggest it.
Okay yeah.
I'm gonna put it on my list.
Uh hold on.
And then I actually need to go.
There's some other things I need to do today.
Uh lobotomy cooperation.
What a fun name.
Okay.
Hmm interesting.
I'm gonna put it on my backlog.
It's a cautious backlog for now.
And you can you can look at this if you want to see what games I've played.
I'm gonna link it here.
You want to see what games I have played?
Uh what games are in my backlog and what I'm playing right now.
I should actually update the one I'm playing right now because it's not quite accurate.
Is Soma on your list?
I've already played Soma.
You jury.
It was fantastic.
Absolutely loved Soma.
Crazy good experience.
I played it many years ago though.
Offstream.
Back before I did YouTube stuff.
I have thought of playing Celeste.
It's on the list too.
Okay.
Yeah I also played Disco Elysium and had a lot of fun with it.
That was back when before they added all the voice lines.
So I'm kind of sad that I played it before they did that.
I should have been more of a patient gamer on that.
Although it was fun to imagine the voices in my head when I was playing it.
Sometimes that makes things more funny than they are with voices.
You know what I mean?
It's like when you're reading a book and you and you imagine a funny situation.
You always imagine the funniest version of that situation.
You know what I mean?
Because it's all in your mind and you make it as funny as you want.
The voice lines were insanely well done.
Hmm.
I believe it.
That game is in general insanely well done.
Alien Isolation is also on my list.
Mr. Beat 93.
I don't know Pentamint, idle villager.
I'm gonna look it up.
Pentamint.
Wow.
16th century narrative in Upper Bavaria.
Okay, well you know what?
Backlog that.
Added to my list of 300 games.
Baba Is You goes Insano style.
I've heard that game is Insano style.
I'm the opposite of a patient gamer.
I play the most broken pre-alpha garbage but it's still kind of fun in its own way.
Well, that's one way to do it.
At least you're on the... you can follow all the memes and all the trends that are happening in the world right at that moment.
Which is something you miss out on when you're a patient gamer.
Which can be really fun.
Hey, someone anonymous gifted a villager a sub.
Thank you.
Whoever that was.
Thank you for that.
We'll get the backlog done by 2147.
Yeah, I just need to go full-time streamer first.
Otherwise that will never happen.
But if I do though, boy am I gonna game every day.
It's gonna be one hell of a cool life.
I mean, I do love my science and all that, but man, if I had the option to just enjoy video games, which is one of my biggest passions in life, I would fucking do it.
Maybe not in a heartbeat.
I would still think about it first, but yeah.
Clone thyself.
Okay guys, I gotta go.
I gotta go.
I really gotta go.
It's so much fun chatting with you guys.
We should do more of this just in general.
Also, I promised to talk or have like a talk with you guys about Undertale and the story and all that.
I have let it sit on my mind, and I've actually changed my mind about a lot of stuff.
Now that I wasn't tired AF after finishing.
So it would be cool to just talk about that, you know, like a little wrap up type of stream, but not a stream dedicated to it.
Just a section of the stream.
I think that would be cool.
If any of you are into that.
I'm not sure when that will be, but soon ish.
For sure.
Yeah.
Definitely.
All right, guys, I'm gonna go.
Thank you to all the followers and all the subscribers.
I really, really appreciate it.
I've gotten so many on Twitch since I started.
It's insane.
I have already made it to where I can apply to be a partner on Twitch.
All because of you guys.
I can already do that now.
That's wild to me, and I am gonna do that.
Yeah, I'm gonna apply for that.
I filled up all the goals already.
You guys did all that.
That's insane.
Okay, I'm out of here.
I'm so glad this game is awesome.
I can't wait to play more of Noida.
It's gonna be a hell of a time.
I'll see you guys around.
Have a good one.
Oh, wait, we got a raid.
That's right.
Let's raid before we go.
Uh, let's see here.
Can I sort by Noida?
Because we got to do that.
Game type.
Category?
Noida.
Let's go with... Oh, oops, I accidentally... Noida.
Okay.
Let's put it on...
Let's put it on someone with just a couple of viewers.
That would be really nice, I think.
Let's see here.
Playing myself?
Yeah.
Let's put it on this guy.
There you go.
Enjoy, guys.
And I'll see you around.